Patient 1	2020.01.24.919183-p27-132.png	"['Figure 1. Chest radiographs of patient 1. a. b. c. d. Chest computed tomographic scans of Patient 1 were obtained on the day of admission (day 6 after the onset of illness). Bilateral focal consolidation, lobar consolidation, and patchy consolidation were clearly observed, especially in the lower lung. ']"
Patient 1	2020.01.24.919183-p27-133.png	"['Figure 1. Chest radiographs of patient 1. a. b. c. d. Chest computed tomographic scans of Patient 1 were obtained on the day of admission (day 6 after the onset of illness). Bilateral focal consolidation, lobar consolidation, and patchy consolidation were clearly observed, especially in the lower lung. ']"
Patient 1	2020.01.24.919183-p27-134.png	"['Figure 1. Chest radiographs of patient 1. a. b. c. d. Chest computed tomographic scans of Patient 1 were obtained on the day of admission (day 6 after the onset of illness). Bilateral focal consolidation, lobar consolidation, and patchy consolidation were clearly observed, especially in the lower lung. ']"
Patient 1	2020.01.24.919183-p27-135.png	"['Figure 1. Chest radiographs of patient 1. a. b. c. d. Chest computed tomographic scans of Patient 1 were obtained on the day of admission (day 6 after the onset of illness). Bilateral focal consolidation, lobar consolidation, and patchy consolidation were clearly observed, especially in the lower lung. ']"
Patient 2	2020.02.10.20021584-p6-52%0.png	"['Figure 1. A 50-year-old man with 2019 novel coronavirus (2019-nCoV) infection. (A) Ground glass shadow in multiple lobes and segments of bilateral lungs, and the lesions were adjacent to the pleura (Illness Day 8, Hospital Day 0). ']"
Patient 2	2020.02.10.20021584-p6-52%1.png	"['Figure 1. A 50-year-old man with 2019 novel coronavirus (2019-nCoV) infection. (A) Ground glass shadow in multiple lobes and segments of bilateral lungs, and the lesions were adjacent to the pleura (Illness Day 8, Hospital Day 0). ']"
Patient 2	2020.02.10.20021584-p6-52%10.png	"['Figure 1. A 50-year-old man with 2019 novel coronavirus (2019-nCoV) infection. (C) Ground glass shadow absorption and reduced consolidation area (Illness Day 15, Hospital Day 7).']"
Patient 2	2020.02.10.20021584-p6-52%11.png	"['Figure 1. A 50-year-old man with 2019 novel coronavirus (2019-nCoV) infection. (C) Ground glass shadow absorption and reduced consolidation area (Illness Day 15, Hospital Day 7).']"
Patient 2	2020.02.10.20021584-p6-52%12.png	"['Figure 1. A 50-year-old man with 2019 novel coronavirus (2019-nCoV) infection. (D) Lesion dissipation (Illness Day 20, Hospital Day 12). ']"
Patient 2	2020.02.10.20021584-p6-52%13.png	"['Figure 1. A 50-year-old man with 2019 novel coronavirus (2019-nCoV) infection. (D) Lesion dissipation (Illness Day 20, Hospital Day 12). ']"
Patient 2	2020.02.10.20021584-p6-52%14.png	"['Figure 1. A 50-year-old man with 2019 novel coronavirus (2019-nCoV) infection. (D) Lesion dissipation (Illness Day 20, Hospital Day 12). ']"
Patient 2	2020.02.10.20021584-p6-52%15.png	"['Figure 1. A 50-year-old man with 2019 novel coronavirus (2019-nCoV) infection. (D) Lesion dissipation (Illness Day 20, Hospital Day 12). ']"
Patient 2	2020.02.10.20021584-p6-52%2.png	"['Figure 1. A 50-year-old man with 2019 novel coronavirus (2019-nCoV) infection. (A) Ground glass shadow in multiple lobes and segments of bilateral lungs, and the lesions were adjacent to the pleura (Illness Day 8, Hospital Day 0). ']"
Patient 2	2020.02.10.20021584-p6-52%3.png	"['Figure 1. A 50-year-old man with 2019 novel coronavirus (2019-nCoV) infection. (A) Ground glass shadow in multiple lobes and segments of bilateral lungs, and the lesions were adjacent to the pleura (Illness Day 8, Hospital Day 0). ']"
Patient 2	2020.02.10.20021584-p6-52%4.png	"['Figure 1. A 50-year-old man with 2019 novel coronavirus (2019-nCoV) infection. (B) Ground glass shadow expanding and consolidation in bilateral lung (Illness Day 11, Hospital Day 3). ']"
Patient 2	2020.02.10.20021584-p6-52%5.png	"['Figure 1. A 50-year-old man with 2019 novel coronavirus (2019-nCoV) infection. (B) Ground glass shadow expanding and consolidation in bilateral lung (Illness Day 11, Hospital Day 3). ']"
Patient 2	2020.02.10.20021584-p6-52%6.png	"['Figure 1. A 50-year-old man with 2019 novel coronavirus (2019-nCoV) infection. (B) Ground glass shadow expanding and consolidation in bilateral lung (Illness Day 11, Hospital Day 3). ']"
Patient 2	2020.02.10.20021584-p6-52%7.png	"['Figure 1. A 50-year-old man with 2019 novel coronavirus (2019-nCoV) infection. (B) Ground glass shadow expanding and consolidation in bilateral lung (Illness Day 11, Hospital Day 3). ']"
Patient 2	2020.02.10.20021584-p6-52%8.png	"['Figure 1. A 50-year-old man with 2019 novel coronavirus (2019-nCoV) infection. (C) Ground glass shadow absorption and reduced consolidation area (Illness Day 15, Hospital Day 7).']"
Patient 2	2020.02.10.20021584-p6-52%9.png	"['Figure 1. A 50-year-old man with 2019 novel coronavirus (2019-nCoV) infection. (C) Ground glass shadow absorption and reduced consolidation area (Illness Day 15, Hospital Day 7).']"
Patient 3	2020.02.11.20021493-p16-109%0.png	"['Figure 2. Computed tomography (CT) scan of the cases 02, 07 and 13.']"
Patient 4	2020.02.11.20021493-p16-109%1.png	"['Figure 2. Computed tomography (CT) scan of the cases 02, 07 and 13.']"
Patient 5	2020.02.11.20021493-p16-109%2.png	"['Figure 2. Computed tomography (CT) scan of the cases 02, 07 and 13.']"
Patient 6	2020.02.11.20022053-p12-67%0.png	"['Figure. Chest Computed tomography (CT) images of patients infected with 2019-nCoV on admission to hospital. A, Chest CT scan obtained on February 2, 2020, from a 39-year-old man, showing bilateral ground glass opacities.']"
Patient 7	2020.02.11.20022053-p12-67%1.png	"['Figure. Chest Computed tomography (CT) images of patients infected with 2019-nCoV on admission to hospital. B, Chest CT scan obtained on February 6, 2020, from a 45-year-old man, showing bilateral ground glass opacities.']"
Patient 8	2020.02.11.20022053-p12-67%2.png	"['Figure. Chest Computed tomography (CT) images of patients infected with 2019-nCoV on admission to hospital. C, Chest CT scan taken on January 27, 2020, from a 48-year-old man (discharged after treatment on day 9), showing patchy shadows.']"
Patient 9	2020.02.11.20022053-p12-67%3.png	"['Figure. Chest Computed tomography (CT) images of patients infected with 2019-nCoV on admission to hospital. D, Chest CT scan taken on January 23, 2020, from a 34-year-old man (discharged after treatment on day 11), showing patchy shadows.']"
Patient 10	2020.02.13.20022673-p13-77%0.png	['Figure 2. Chest computed tomographic Images of patients with SARS-CoV-2 and other pathogens. ']
Patient 11	2020.02.13.20022673-p13-77%1.png	['Figure 2. Chest computed tomographic Images of patients with SARS-CoV-2 and other pathogens. ']
Patient 12	2020.02.13.20022673-p13-77%2.png	['Figure 2. Chest computed tomographic Images of patients with SARS-CoV-2 and other pathogens. ']
Patient 13	2020.02.17.20024018-p17-61%0.png	['The Imageology change with the disease progression of a 36 years-old female severe patient infected with 2019-CoV A and B were second day of the course of disease; C and D were day 7; E was day 11 and F was day 15. A. CT showed local ground glass shadow and nodules.']
Patient 13	2020.02.17.20024018-p17-61%1.png	['The Imageology change with the disease progression of a 36 years-old female severe patient infected with 2019-CoV A and B were second day of the course of disease; C and D were day 7; E was day 11 and F was day 15. B. Thin ground glass shadow Mainly distributed in outer zone of the lung and under the pleura.']
Patient 13	2020.02.17.20024018-p17-61%2.png	"['The Imageology change with the disease progression of a 36 years-old female severe patient infected with 2019-CoV A and B were second day of the course of disease; C and D were day 7; E was day 11 and F was day 15. C. Ground glass shadow of both lungs, left pulmonary nodule focus located under pleura.']"
Patient 13	2020.02.17.20024018-p17-61%3.png	['The Imageology change with the disease progression of a 36 years-old female severe patient infected with 2019-CoV A and B were second day of the course of disease; C and D were day 7; E was day 11 and F was day 15. D. Progress to patchy shadow with uneven density.']
Patient 13	2020.02.17.20024018-p17-61%4.png	"['The Imageology change with the disease progression of a 36 years-old female severe patient infected with 2019-CoV A and B were second day of the course of disease; C and D were day 7; E was day 11 and F was day 15. E. Multiple patchy shadows with fuzzy edges were observed, and large ground glass shadow and condensation shadow were found in both lower lobe.']"
Patient 14	2020.02.19.20025023-p20-93%0.png	['Figure 1. Chest computed tomographic images of patients with coronavirus disease 2019 (A) Mild pneumonia patient showed patchy ground-glass opacity with clear borderline in a transverse chest CT image.']
Patient 15	2020.02.19.20025023-p20-93%1.png	['Figure 1. Chest computed tomographic images of patients with coronavirus disease 2019 (B-C) Transverse chest CT images of moderate patients showing large ground-glass opacities and some with ambiguous borderline.']
Patient 16	2020.02.19.20025023-p20-93%2.png	['Figure 1. Chest computed tomographic images of patients with coronavirus disease 2019 (B-C) Transverse chest CT images of moderate patients showing large ground-glass opacities and some with ambiguous borderline.']
Patient 17	2020.02.19.20025023-p20-93%3.png	['Figure 1. Chest computed tomographic images of patients with coronavirus disease 2019 (D) Severe cases were characterized by typical white lung change as high-density mass shadows and multiple lobular consolidations were observed.']
Patient 18	2020.02.22.20024927-p18-66%0.png	"['A sample scoring on CT images of a 63-year-old woman from mortality group demonstrated a total score of 63. It was calculated as: for upper zone (A), 3 (consolidation) × 3 (50-75% distribution) × 2 (both right and left lungs) + 2 (ground glass opacity) ×1 (< 25% distribution) × 2 (both right and left lungs); for middle zone. ']"
Patient 18	2020.02.22.20024927-p18-66%1.png	"['A sample scoring on CT images of a 63-year-old woman from mortality group demonstrated a total score of 63. It was calculated as: for upper zone (B), 3 (consolidation) × 2 (25-50% distribution) × 2 (both right and left lungs) + 2 (ground glass opacity) × 2 (25-50% distribution) × 2 (both right and left lungs) ; for lower zone. ']"
Patient 18	2020.02.22.20024927-p18-66%2.png	"['A sample scoring on CT images of a 63-year-old woman from mortality group demonstrated a total score of 63. It was calculated as: for upper zone (C), 3 (consolidation) × (2 (25-50% distribution of the right lung) + 3 (50-75% distribution of the left lung))  + 2 (ground glass opacity) × (2 (25-50% distribution of the right lung) + 1 (< 25% distribution of the left lung)). ']"
Patient 19	2020.02.22.20024927-p19-68%0.png	['CT images of a 76-year-old woman from survival group showed pure ground glass opacities with predominant peripheral distribution in middle and lower lung zones (A-C).']
Patient 19	2020.02.22.20024927-p19-68%1.png	['CT images of a 76-year-old woman from survival group showed pure ground glass opacities with predominant peripheral distribution in middle and lower lung zones (A-C).']
Patient 19	2020.02.22.20024927-p19-68%2.png	['CT images of a 76-year-old woman from survival group showed pure ground glass opacities with predominant peripheral distribution in middle and lower lung zones (A-C).']
Patient 20	2020.02.22.20024927-p19-68%3.png	"['Air bronchogram, together with extensive of consolidations and ground glass opacities were found in the CT images of a 72–year-old woman from mortality group (D-F).']"
Patient 20	2020.02.22.20024927-p19-68%4.png	"['Air bronchogram, together with extensive of consolidations and ground glass opacities were found in the CT images of a 72–year-old woman from mortality group (D-F).']"
Patient 20	2020.02.22.20024927-p19-68%5.png	"['Air bronchogram, together with extensive of consolidations and ground glass opacities were found in the CT images of a 72–year-old woman from mortality group (D-F).']"
Patient 21	2020.02.22.20024927-p20-70%0.png	['Two cases of CT images from survival group showed ground glass nodular opacities on admission and progressed to multiple patchy ground glass opacities on reexamination. The CT images of a 60-year-old woman on admission showed peripherally distributed focal ground glass nodular opacities in only right lung (A) and rechecked CT images showed expanded area of patchy ground glass opacities in both right and left lungs with reticular and interlobular septal thickening on 7 days later (B). ']
Patient 21	2020.02.22.20024927-p20-70%1.png	['Two cases of CT images from survival group showed ground glass nodular opacities on admission and progressed to multiple patchy ground glass opacities on reexamination. The CT images of a 60-year-old woman on admission showed peripherally distributed focal ground glass nodular opacities in only right lung (A) and rechecked CT images showed expanded area of patchy ground glass opacities in both right and left lungs with reticular and interlobular septal thickening on 7 days later (B). ']
Patient 22	2020.02.22.20024927-p20-70%2.png	['Two cases of CT images from survival group showed ground glass nodular opacities on admission and progressed to multiple patchy ground glass opacities on reexamination. Unilateral ground glass nodular opacity was found on CT images of a 64-year-old man from survival group (C) and progressed patchy ground glass opacities as well as interlobular septal thickening were seen after 4 days (D). ']
Patient 22	2020.02.22.20024927-p20-70%3.png	['Two cases of CT images from survival group showed ground glass nodular opacities on admission and progressed to multiple patchy ground glass opacities on reexamination. Unilateral ground glass nodular opacity was found on CT images of a 64-year-old man from survival group (C) and progressed patchy ground glass opacities as well as interlobular septal thickening were seen after 4 days (D). ']
Patient 23	2020.02.23.20026856-p17-115%0.png	"['Figure 1. Transverse chest CT from a 39 year-old man, showing ground-glass opacities of bilateral lungs near the pleura (a and b) on day 1 from symptom onset, and increased bilateral ground-glass opacities and consolidation(c and d) on day 5  from symptom onset, and slightly absorbed ground-glass opacities (e and f) on day 7 from symptom onset after 7-day treatment.']"
Patient 23	2020.02.23.20026856-p17-115%1.png	"['Figure 1. Transverse chest CT from a 39 year-old man, showing ground-glass opacities of bilateral lungs near the pleura (a and b) on day 1 from symptom onset, and increased bilateral ground-glass opacities and consolidation(c and d) on day 5  from symptom onset, and slightly absorbed ground-glass opacities (e and f) on day 7 from symptom onset after 7-day treatment.']"
Patient 23	2020.02.23.20026856-p17-115%2.png	"['Figure 1. Transverse chest CT from a 39 year-old man, showing ground-glass opacities of bilateral lungs near the pleura (a and b) on day 1 from symptom onset, and increased bilateral ground-glass opacities and consolidation(c and d) on day 5  from symptom onset, and slightly absorbed ground-glass opacities (e and f) on day 7 from symptom onset after 7-day treatment.']"
Patient 23	2020.02.23.20026856-p17-115%3.png	"['Figure 1. Transverse chest CT from a 39 year-old man, showing ground-glass opacities of bilateral lungs near the pleura (a and b) on day 1 from symptom onset, and increased bilateral ground-glass opacities and consolidation(c and d) on day 5  from symptom onset, and slightly absorbed ground-glass opacities (e and f) on day 7 from symptom onset after 7-day treatment.']"
Patient 23	2020.02.23.20026856-p17-115%4.png	"['Figure 1. Transverse chest CT from a 39 year-old man, showing ground-glass opacities of bilateral lungs near the pleura (a and b) on day 1 from symptom onset, and increased bilateral ground-glass opacities and consolidation(c and d) on day 5  from symptom onset, and slightly absorbed ground-glass opacities (e and f) on day 7 from symptom onset after 7-day treatment.']"
Patient 23	2020.02.23.20026856-p17-115%5.png	"['Figure 1. Transverse chest CT from a 39 year-old man, showing ground-glass opacities of bilateral lungs near the pleura (a and b) on day 1 from symptom onset, and increased bilateral ground-glass opacities and consolidation(c and d) on day 5  from symptom onset, and slightly absorbed ground-glass opacities (e and f) on day 7 from symptom onset after 7-day treatment.']"
Patient 24	2020.02.24.20027052-p8-73%0.png	"['Figure 4. Quantification of EAT density by CT scan. CT scan examples of the patients from light (a), mild (b), severe (c) and critical (d) group of COVID-19 patients. Dark red areas represent the EATs, and blue areas indicate other heart tissues. Red arrows indicate lung lesions, and ground-glass opacity features are obviously presented in severe (c) and critical (d) groups (marked with red arrow). Scale bar, 10 cm. ']"
Patient 25	2020.02.24.20027052-p8-73%1.png	"['Figure 4. Quantification of EAT density by CT scan. CT scan examples of the patients from light (a), mild (b), severe (c) and critical (d) group of COVID-19 patients. Dark red areas represent the EATs, and blue areas indicate other heart tissues. Red arrows indicate lung lesions, and ground-glass opacity features are obviously presented in severe (c) and critical (d) groups (marked with red arrow). Scale bar, 10 cm. ']"
Patient 26	2020.02.24.20027052-p8-73%2.png	"['Figure 4. Quantification of EAT density by CT scan. CT scan examples of the patients from light (a), mild (b), severe (c) and critical (d) group of COVID-19 patients. Dark red areas represent the EATs, and blue areas indicate other heart tissues. Red arrows indicate lung lesions, and ground-glass opacity features are obviously presented in severe (c) and critical (d) groups (marked with red arrow). Scale bar, 10 cm. ']"
Patient 27	2020.02.24.20027052-p8-73%3.png	"['Figure 4. Quantification of EAT density by CT scan. CT scan examples of the patients from light (a), mild (b), severe (c) and critical (d) group of COVID-19 patients. Dark red areas represent the EATs, and blue areas indicate other heart tissues. Red arrows indicate lung lesions, and ground-glass opacity features are obviously presented in severe (c) and critical (d) groups (marked with red arrow). Scale bar, 10 cm. ']"
Patient 28	2020.02.24.20027201-p19-669.png	['Figure 3. Representative images of chest CT scans (the transverse plane). Patients with COVID-19 had unilateral or bilateral pneumonia. The multiple “ground-glass” lesions were the characteristics of COVID-19 pneumonia.The green arrows represent the sites of lesions.']
Patient 29	2020.02.24.20027201-p19-670.png	['Figure 3. Representative images of chest CT scans (the transverse plane). Patients with COVID-19 had unilateral or bilateral pneumonia. The multiple “ground-glass” lesions were the characteristics of COVID-19 pneumonia.The green arrows represent the sites of lesions.']
Patient 30	2020.02.25.20021568-p23-108%0.png	"['Figure 3. Processing and prediction schematic of the model. Raw images were firstly input into the model, and after processing of the model, prediction boxes framing suspicious lesions were output. Valid areas were further extracted and unnecessary fields were filter out to avoid possible false positives. To predict by case, a logic linking the prediction results of consecutive images was added. Computed tomography (CT) images with the above prediction results were divided into four quadrants, and results would be output only when three consecutive images were predicted to have lesions in the same quadrant. ']"
Patient 31	2020.02.25.20021568-p23-108%1.png	"['Figure 3. Processing and prediction schematic of the model. Raw images were firstly input into the model, and after processing of the model, prediction boxes framing suspicious lesions were output. Valid areas were further extracted and unnecessary fields were filter out to avoid possible false positives. To predict by case, a logic linking the prediction results of consecutive images was added. Computed tomography (CT) images with the above prediction results were divided into four quadrants, and results would be output only when three consecutive images were predicted to have lesions in the same quadrant. ']"
Patient 32	2020.02.25.20021568-p23-108%10.png	"['Figure 3. Processing and prediction schematic of the model. Raw images were firstly input into the model, and after processing of the model, prediction boxes framing suspicious lesions were output. Valid areas were further extracted and unnecessary fields were filter out to avoid possible false positives. To predict by case, a logic linking the prediction results of consecutive images was added. Computed tomography (CT) images with the above prediction results were divided into four quadrants, and results would be output only when three consecutive images were predicted to have lesions in the same quadrant. ']"
Patient 33	2020.02.25.20021568-p23-108%11.png	"['Figure 3. Processing and prediction schematic of the model. Raw images were firstly input into the model, and after processing of the model, prediction boxes framing suspicious lesions were output. Valid areas were further extracted and unnecessary fields were filter out to avoid possible false positives. To predict by case, a logic linking the prediction results of consecutive images was added. Computed tomography (CT) images with the above prediction results were divided into four quadrants, and results would be output only when three consecutive images were predicted to have lesions in the same quadrant. ']"
Patient 34	2020.02.25.20021568-p23-108%12.png	"['Figure 3. Processing and prediction schematic of the model. Raw images were firstly input into the model, and after processing of the model, prediction boxes framing suspicious lesions were output. Valid areas were further extracted and unnecessary fields were filter out to avoid possible false positives. To predict by case, a logic linking the prediction results of consecutive images was added. Computed tomography (CT) images with the above prediction results were divided into four quadrants, and results would be output only when three consecutive images were predicted to have lesions in the same quadrant. ']"
Patient 35	2020.02.25.20021568-p23-108%13.png	"['Figure 3. Processing and prediction schematic of the model. Raw images were firstly input into the model, and after processing of the model, prediction boxes framing suspicious lesions were output. Valid areas were further extracted and unnecessary fields were filter out to avoid possible false positives. To predict by case, a logic linking the prediction results of consecutive images was added. Computed tomography (CT) images with the above prediction results were divided into four quadrants, and results would be output only when three consecutive images were predicted to have lesions in the same quadrant. ']"
Patient 36	2020.02.25.20021568-p23-108%14.png	"['Figure 3. Processing and prediction schematic of the model. Raw images were firstly input into the model, and after processing of the model, prediction boxes framing suspicious lesions were output. Valid areas were further extracted and unnecessary fields were filter out to avoid possible false positives. To predict by case, a logic linking the prediction results of consecutive images was added. Computed tomography (CT) images with the above prediction results were divided into four quadrants, and results would be output only when three consecutive images were predicted to have lesions in the same quadrant. ']"
Patient 37	2020.02.25.20021568-p23-108%15.png	"['Figure 3. Processing and prediction schematic of the model. Raw images were firstly input into the model, and after processing of the model, prediction boxes framing suspicious lesions were output. Valid areas were further extracted and unnecessary fields were filter out to avoid possible false positives. To predict by case, a logic linking the prediction results of consecutive images was added. Computed tomography (CT) images with the above prediction results were divided into four quadrants, and results would be output only when three consecutive images were predicted to have lesions in the same quadrant. ']"
Patient 38	2020.02.25.20021568-p23-108%2.png	"['Figure 3. Processing and prediction schematic of the model. Raw images were firstly input into the model, and after processing of the model, prediction boxes framing suspicious lesions were output. Valid areas were further extracted and unnecessary fields were filter out to avoid possible false positives. To predict by case, a logic linking the prediction results of consecutive images was added. Computed tomography (CT) images with the above prediction results were divided into four quadrants, and results would be output only when three consecutive images were predicted to have lesions in the same quadrant. ']"
Patient 39	2020.02.25.20021568-p23-108%3.png	"['Figure 3. Processing and prediction schematic of the model. Raw images were firstly input into the model, and after processing of the model, prediction boxes framing suspicious lesions were output. Valid areas were further extracted and unnecessary fields were filter out to avoid possible false positives. To predict by case, a logic linking the prediction results of consecutive images was added. Computed tomography (CT) images with the above prediction results were divided into four quadrants, and results would be output only when three consecutive images were predicted to have lesions in the same quadrant. ']"
Patient 40	2020.02.25.20021568-p23-108%4.png	"['Figure 3. Processing and prediction schematic of the model. Raw images were firstly input into the model, and after processing of the model, prediction boxes framing suspicious lesions were output. Valid areas were further extracted and unnecessary fields were filter out to avoid possible false positives. To predict by case, a logic linking the prediction results of consecutive images was added. Computed tomography (CT) images with the above prediction results were divided into four quadrants, and results would be output only when three consecutive images were predicted to have lesions in the same quadrant. ']"
Patient 41	2020.02.25.20021568-p23-108%5.png	"['Figure 3. Processing and prediction schematic of the model. Raw images were firstly input into the model, and after processing of the model, prediction boxes framing suspicious lesions were output. Valid areas were further extracted and unnecessary fields were filter out to avoid possible false positives. To predict by case, a logic linking the prediction results of consecutive images was added. Computed tomography (CT) images with the above prediction results were divided into four quadrants, and results would be output only when three consecutive images were predicted to have lesions in the same quadrant. ']"
Patient 42	2020.02.25.20021568-p23-108%6.png	"['Figure 3. Processing and prediction schematic of the model. Raw images were firstly input into the model, and after processing of the model, prediction boxes framing suspicious lesions were output. Valid areas were further extracted and unnecessary fields were filter out to avoid possible false positives. To predict by case, a logic linking the prediction results of consecutive images was added. Computed tomography (CT) images with the above prediction results were divided into four quadrants, and results would be output only when three consecutive images were predicted to have lesions in the same quadrant. ']"
Patient 43	2020.02.25.20021568-p23-108%7.png	"['Figure 3. Processing and prediction schematic of the model. Raw images were firstly input into the model, and after processing of the model, prediction boxes framing suspicious lesions were output. Valid areas were further extracted and unnecessary fields were filter out to avoid possible false positives. To predict by case, a logic linking the prediction results of consecutive images was added. Computed tomography (CT) images with the above prediction results were divided into four quadrants, and results would be output only when three consecutive images were predicted to have lesions in the same quadrant. ']"
Patient 44	2020.02.25.20021568-p23-108%8.png	"['Figure 3. Processing and prediction schematic of the model. Raw images were firstly input into the model, and after processing of the model, prediction boxes framing suspicious lesions were output. Valid areas were further extracted and unnecessary fields were filter out to avoid possible false positives. To predict by case, a logic linking the prediction results of consecutive images was added. Computed tomography (CT) images with the above prediction results were divided into four quadrants, and results would be output only when three consecutive images were predicted to have lesions in the same quadrant. ']"
Patient 45	2020.02.25.20021568-p23-108%9.png	"['Figure 3. Processing and prediction schematic of the model. Raw images were firstly input into the model, and after processing of the model, prediction boxes framing suspicious lesions were output. Valid areas were further extracted and unnecessary fields were filter out to avoid possible false positives. To predict by case, a logic linking the prediction results of consecutive images was added. Computed tomography (CT) images with the above prediction results were divided into four quadrants, and results would be output only when three consecutive images were predicted to have lesions in the same quadrant. ']"
Patient 46	2020.02.25.20021568-p24-111%0.png	"['Figure 4. Representative images of the model's predictions. A. Computed tomography (CT) images of COVID19 pneumonia. The predictions between the artificial intelligence model and radiologists were consistent. Green boxes, labels from radiologists; red boxes, labels from the model.']"
Patient 47	2020.02.25.20021568-p24-111%1.png	"['Figure 4. Representative images of the model's predictions. A. Computed tomography (CT) images of COVID19 pneumonia. The predictions between the artificial intelligence model and radiologists were consistent. Green boxes, labels from radiologists; red boxes, labels from the model.']"
Patient 48	2020.02.25.20021568-p24-111%2.png	"['Figure 4. Representative images of the model's predictions. A. Computed tomography (CT) images of COVID19 pneumonia. The predictions between the artificial intelligence model and radiologists were consistent. Green boxes, labels from radiologists; red boxes, labels from the model.']"
Patient 49	2020.02.25.20021568-p24-111%3.png	"['Figure 4. Representative images of the model's predictions. A. Computed tomography (CT) images of COVID19 pneumonia. The predictions between the artificial intelligence model and radiologists were consistent. Green boxes, labels from radiologists; red boxes, labels from the model.']"
Patient 50	2020.02.25.20021568-p24-111%4.png	"['Figure 4. Representative images of the model's predictions. A. Computed tomography (CT) images of COVID19 pneumonia. The predictions between the artificial intelligence model and radiologists were consistent. Green boxes, labels from radiologists; red boxes, labels from the model.']"
Patient 51	2020.02.25.20021568-p24-111%5.png	"['Figure 4. Representative images of the model's predictions. B. CT images of the control. The first image is an ordinary bacterial pneumonia, showing a consolidation of the right lower lobe. The second image has a tumorous lesion in the lung, showing a mass in the left upper lobe, with burrs seen at the edges, and showing leaf-like growth with vacuoles inside. The third image is a secondary pulmonary tuberculosis, showing a left apical fibrous cord. The fourth image is a bronchiectasis complicated with infection, showing bronchodilation and expansion, cystic changes, and surrounding patches of infection. The fifth image shows normal lungs. ']"
Patient 52	2020.02.25.20021568-p24-111%6.png	"['Figure 4. Representative images of the model's predictions. B. CT images of the control. The first image is an ordinary bacterial pneumonia, showing a consolidation of the right lower lobe. The second image has a tumorous lesion in the lung, showing a mass in the left upper lobe, with burrs seen at the edges, and showing leaf-like growth with vacuoles inside. The third image is a secondary pulmonary tuberculosis, showing a left apical fibrous cord. The fourth image is a bronchiectasis complicated with infection, showing bronchodilation and expansion, cystic changes, and surrounding patches of infection. The fifth image shows normal lungs. ']"
Patient 53	2020.02.25.20021568-p24-111%7.png	"['Figure 4. Representative images of the model's predictions. B. CT images of the control. The first image is an ordinary bacterial pneumonia, showing a consolidation of the right lower lobe. The second image has a tumorous lesion in the lung, showing a mass in the left upper lobe, with burrs seen at the edges, and showing leaf-like growth with vacuoles inside. The third image is a secondary pulmonary tuberculosis, showing a left apical fibrous cord. The fourth image is a bronchiectasis complicated with infection, showing bronchodilation and expansion, cystic changes, and surrounding patches of infection. The fifth image shows normal lungs. ']"
Patient 54	2020.02.25.20021568-p24-111%8.png	"['Figure 4. Representative images of the model's predictions. B. CT images of the control. The first image is an ordinary bacterial pneumonia, showing a consolidation of the right lower lobe. The second image has a tumorous lesion in the lung, showing a mass in the left upper lobe, with burrs seen at the edges, and showing leaf-like growth with vacuoles inside. The third image is a secondary pulmonary tuberculosis, showing a left apical fibrous cord. The fourth image is a bronchiectasis complicated with infection, showing bronchodilation and expansion, cystic changes, and surrounding patches of infection. The fifth image shows normal lungs. ']"
Patient 55	2020.02.25.20021568-p24-111%9.png	"['Figure 4. Representative images of the model's predictions. B. CT images of the control. The first image is an ordinary bacterial pneumonia, showing a consolidation of the right lower lobe. The second image has a tumorous lesion in the lung, showing a mass in the left upper lobe, with burrs seen at the edges, and showing leaf-like growth with vacuoles inside. The third image is a secondary pulmonary tuberculosis, showing a left apical fibrous cord. The fourth image is a bronchiectasis complicated with infection, showing bronchodilation and expansion, cystic changes, and surrounding patches of infection. The fifth image shows normal lungs. ']"
Patient 56	2020.02.25.20027763-p15-53%0.png	['Figure 2. CT findings in 4 patients with confirmed COVID-19. A. Patchy GGO distributed in subpleural area in left lower lung.']
Patient 57	2020.02.25.20027763-p15-53%1.png	"['Figure 2. CT findings in 4 patients with confirmed COVID-19. B. A round-like, mixed GGO and consolidation lesion (with reversed halo sign) in subpleural area in right lower lung.']"
Patient 58	2020.02.26.20026989-p34-114_1%0.png	"['Figure 3. The relationship of pulmonary inflammation and CRSL characteristics after COVID-19 infected.  A. Computed tomography of the chest of patients with COVID-19. According to the patchy or ground glass shadows in the chest CT images, the patients were divided into < 5 0 % and ≥ 5 0 % groups.']"
Patient 59	2020.02.26.20026989-p34-114_1%1.png	"['Figure 3. The relationship of pulmonary inflammation and CRSL characteristics after COVID-19 infected.  A. Computed tomography of the chest of patients with COVID-19. According to the patchy or ground glass shadows in the chest CT images, the patients were divided into < 5 0 % and ≥ 5 0 % groups.']"
Patient 60	2020.02.26.20026989-p34-114_2%0.png	"['Figure 3. The relationship of pulmonary inflammation and CRSL characteristics after COVID-19 infected.  A. Computed tomography of the chest of patients with COVID-19. According to the patchy or ground glass shadows in the chest CT images, the patients were divided into < 5 0 % and ≥ 5 0 % groups.']"
Patient 61	2020.02.26.20026989-p34-114_2%1.png	"['Figure 3. The relationship of pulmonary inflammation and CRSL characteristics after COVID-19 infected.  A. Computed tomography of the chest of patients with COVID-19. According to the patchy or ground glass shadows in the chest CT images, the patients were divided into < 5 0 % and ≥ 5 0 % groups.']"
Patient 62	2020.02.26.20027938-p6-80_1%0.png	"['Fig. 3 Clinical photographs of the positive patient regarding conjunctivitis and chest CT: (D-F)dynamic changes of peripheral ground-glass opacities in both lungs (yellow arrows) which illuminate the pneumonia caused by SARS-COV-2 infection.The pulmonary lesions were aggravated on the 10th day, and the lesions were basically absorbed on the 18th day. ']"
Patient 62	2020.02.26.20027938-p6-80_1%1.png	"['Fig. 3 Clinical photographs of the positive patient regarding conjunctivitis and chest CT: (D-F)dynamic changes of peripheral ground-glass opacities in both lungs (yellow arrows) which illuminate the pneumonia caused by SARS-COV-2 infection.The pulmonary lesions were aggravated on the 10th day, and the lesions were basically absorbed on the 18th day. ']"
Patient 62	2020.02.26.20027938-p6-80_2%0.png	"['Fig. 3 Clinical photographs of the positive patient regarding conjunctivitis and chest CT: (D-F)dynamic changes of peripheral ground-glass opacities in both lungs (yellow arrows) which illuminate the pneumonia caused by SARS-COV-2 infection.The pulmonary lesions were aggravated on the 10th day, and the lesions were basically absorbed on the 18th day. ']"
Patient 62	2020.02.26.20027938-p6-80_2%1.png	"['Fig. 3 Clinical photographs of the positive patient regarding conjunctivitis and chest CT: (D-F)dynamic changes of peripheral ground-glass opacities in both lungs (yellow arrows) which illuminate the pneumonia caused by SARS-COV-2 infection.The pulmonary lesions were aggravated on the 10th day, and the lesions were basically absorbed on the 18th day. ']"
Patient 62	2020.02.26.20027938-p6-80_3%0.png	"['Fig. 3 Clinical photographs of the positive patient regarding conjunctivitis and chest CT: (D-F)dynamic changes of peripheral ground-glass opacities in both lungs (yellow arrows) which illuminate the pneumonia caused by SARS-COV-2 infection.The pulmonary lesions were aggravated on the 10th day, and the lesions were basically absorbed on the 18th day. ']"
Patient 62	2020.02.26.20027938-p6-80_3%1.png	"['Fig. 3 Clinical photographs of the positive patient regarding conjunctivitis and chest CT: (D-F)dynamic changes of peripheral ground-glass opacities in both lungs (yellow arrows) which illuminate the pneumonia caused by SARS-COV-2 infection.The pulmonary lesions were aggravated on the 10th day, and the lesions were basically absorbed on the 18th day. ']"
Patient 63	2020.02.27.20027557-p25-137%0.png	['Figure 4. Chest CT images in the axial (left panel) and coronal view (right panel) of represented severe COVID-19 patient before and after receiving DIP adjunctive therapy. (A) Initial chest CT scan 10 days before DIP treatment.']
Patient 63	2020.02.27.20027557-p25-137%1.png	['Figure 4. Chest CT images in the axial (left panel) and coronal view (right panel) of represented severe COVID-19 patient before and after receiving DIP adjunctive therapy. (B) Chest CT scan 5 days before DIP treatment.']
Patient 63	2020.02.27.20027557-p25-137%2.png	['Figure 4. Chest CT images in the axial (left panel) and coronal view (right panel) of represented severe COVID-19 patient before and after receiving DIP adjunctive therapy. (C) Chest CT scan 2 days before DIP treatment.']
Patient 63	2020.02.27.20027557-p25-137%3.png	['Figure 4. Chest CT images in the axial (left panel) and coronal view (right panel) of represented severe COVID-19 patient before and after receiving DIP adjunctive therapy. (D) Chest CT scan 2 days after DIP treatment.']
Patient 63	2020.02.27.20027557-p25-137%4.png	['Figure 4. Chest CT images in the axial (left panel) and coronal view (right panel) of represented severe COVID-19 patient before and after receiving DIP adjunctive therapy. (E) Chest CT scan 7 days after DIP treatment.']
Patient 64	2020.02.28.20029025-p23-182.png	"['Figure 7. Patient case CT scan. A: Patient ID 55, the nucleic acid detection result was negative, but the IgM and IgG results were positive. In the lower of both lungs, there were large fuzzy shadows and GGO, some slightly fan-shaped distribution. ']"
Patient 65	2020.02.28.20029025-p23-183.png	"['Figure 7. Patient case CT scan. B: Patient ID 19, the nucleic acid detection result was positive, but the IgM and IgG results were negative, no obvious lesion was found in both lungs. ']"
Patient 66	2020.03.01.20029769-p21-73_1%0.png	"['Figure 4 Variation in IL-6 and chest computed tomography in severe COVID-19 patients. (A) The elevated baseline IL-6 was correlated with the severity assessed by chest computed tomography (CT) scan, and the decrease in IL-6 after treatment was positively correlated with the improvement in chest CT images. ']"
Patient 67	2020.03.01.20029769-p21-73_1%1.png	"['Figure 4 Variation in IL-6 and chest computed tomography in severe COVID-19 patients. (A) The elevated baseline IL-6 was correlated with the severity assessed by chest computed tomography (CT) scan, and the decrease in IL-6 after treatment was positively correlated with the improvement in chest CT images. ']"
Patient 68	2020.03.01.20029769-p21-73_1%2.png	"['Figure 4 Variation in IL-6 and chest computed tomography in severe COVID-19 patients. (A) The elevated baseline IL-6 was correlated with the severity assessed by chest computed tomography (CT) scan, and the decrease in IL-6 after treatment was positively correlated with the improvement in chest CT images. ']"
Patient 69	2020.03.01.20029769-p21-73_2%0.png	"['Figure 4 Variation in IL-6 and chest computed tomography in severe COVID-19 patients. (A) The elevated baseline IL-6 was correlated with the severity assessed by chest computed tomography (CT) scan, and the decrease in IL-6 after treatment was positively correlated with the improvement in chest CT images. ']"
Patient 70	2020.03.01.20029769-p21-73_2%1.png	"['Figure 4 Variation in IL-6 and chest computed tomography in severe COVID-19 patients. (A) The elevated baseline IL-6 was correlated with the severity assessed by chest computed tomography (CT) scan, and the decrease in IL-6 after treatment was positively correlated with the improvement in chest CT images. ']"
Patient 71	2020.03.01.20029769-p21-73_2%2.png	"['Figure 4 Variation in IL-6 and chest computed tomography in severe COVID-19 patients. (A) The elevated baseline IL-6 was correlated with the severity assessed by chest computed tomography (CT) scan, and the decrease in IL-6 after treatment was positively correlated with the improvement in chest CT images. ']"
Patient 72	2020.03.01.20029769-p21-73_3.png	"['Figure 4 Variation in IL-6 and chest computed tomography in severe COVID-19 patients. (B) Three patients showed elevated IL-6 after treatment, which is associated with disease exacerbation and progressed CT imaging. ']"
Patient 73	2020.03.01.20029769-p21-73_4.png	"['Figure 4 Variation in IL-6 and chest computed tomography in severe COVID-19 patients. (B) Three patients showed elevated IL-6 after treatment, which is associated with disease exacerbation and progressed CT imaging. ']"
Patient 74	2020.03.03.20030353-p17-106%0.png	['Figure 1. The typical manifestations in CT and chest X-ray for patients with COVID-19. Cross-sectional CT shows (A) patchy consolidation abutting the pleura in left upper lobe.  ']
Patient 75	2020.03.03.20030353-p17-106%1.png	['Figure 1. The typical manifestations in CT and chest X-ray for patients with COVID-19. Cross-sectional CT shows (B) large areas of consolidation with air bronchogram sign in right upper lobe.  ']
Patient 76	2020.03.03.20030353-p17-106%2.png	['Figure 1. The typical manifestations in CT and chest X-ray for patients with COVID-19. Cross-sectional CT shows (C) Ground glass opacity in bilateral upper lobe.  ']
Patient 77	2020.03.03.20030668-p18-64%0.png	['Figure 1 Typical chest radiographs of a patient. Chest radiographs of one patient on day 1 at ICU admission (A) and day 5 (B); CT scan of chest of the same patient on day 10 and day 20 after ICU admission. ']
Patient 77	2020.03.03.20030668-p18-64%1.png	['Figure 1 Typical chest radiographs of a patient. Chest radiographs of one patient on day 1 at ICU admission (A) and day 5 (B); CT scan of chest of the same patient on day 10 and day 20 after ICU admission. ']
Patient 78	2020.03.03.20030775-p10-88%0.png	"['Figure2. 57-year old man with history of recent travel to Wuhan, presenting with fever, cough and shortness of breath. Axial thin-section non-contrast CT scan shows diffuse bilateral confluent and patchy ground-glass, air-bronchogram and consolidation, characterized by peripheral distribution. Multiple lobes were involved.']"
Patient 78	2020.03.03.20030775-p10-88%1.png	"['Figure2. 57-year old man with history of recent travel to Wuhan, presenting with fever, cough and shortness of breath. Axial thin-section non-contrast CT scan shows diffuse bilateral confluent and patchy ground-glass, air-bronchogram and consolidation, characterized by peripheral distribution. Multiple lobes were involved.']"
Patient 79	2020.03.03.20030775-p11-90%0.png	"['Figure 4. 57-year old man as mild NCP patients with history of recent travel to Wuhan. Ground-glass opacities with a peripheral distribution in bilateral lung (green arrow), and with enlarged image in the upper right corner of A image. Vascular enlargement sign was observed in the lesion located in the left upper lobe, and with enlarged image in the upper left corner of B image (yellow arrow). The lesions in the left lower lobe shows cobblestone/reticular pattern, and with enlarged image in the lower right corner of B image (red yellow).']"
Patient 79	2020.03.03.20030775-p11-90%1.png	"['Figure 4. 57-year old man as mild NCP patients with history of recent travel to Wuhan. Ground-glass opacities with a peripheral distribution in bilateral lung (green arrow), and with enlarged image in the upper right corner of A image. Vascular enlargement sign was observed in the lesion located in the left upper lobe, and with enlarged image in the upper left corner of B image (yellow arrow). The lesions in the left lower lobe shows cobblestone/reticular pattern, and with enlarged image in the lower right corner of B image (red yellow).']"
Patient 80	2020.03.03.20030775-p11-91.png	"['Figure 3. 76-year old man with history of recent travel to Wuhan, presenting with fever and productive cough. Axial thin-section non-contrast CT image shows diffusion lesions in bilateral lung, mainly manifested as ground-glass opacification (red arrow and red line around region), and cobble stone/Reticular pattern (blue arrow and blue line around region). Besides, Vascular enlargement sign was observed in the lesions (yellow arrow).']"
Patient 81	2020.03.03.20030775-p12-93%0.png	"['Figure5. 68-year old female as serve NCP patients with history of recent travel to Wuhan, presenting with fever and productive cough. Axial thin-section non-contrast CT image shows diffusion lesions in bilateral lung. A showed many CT features such as ground-glass opacification, cobblestone/reticular pattern (blue arrow and blue line around region), fibrosis and dilated bronchi with thickened wall (the enlarged image in the upper right corner, red arrow). B showed consolidation (pink arrow) and mixed pattern (yellow arrow and yellow line around region) in the bilateral lower lobes.']"
Patient 81	2020.03.03.20030775-p12-93%1.png	"['Figure5. 68-year old female as serve NCP patients with history of recent travel to Wuhan, presenting with fever and productive cough. Axial thin-section non-contrast CT image shows diffusion lesions in bilateral lung. A showed many CT features such as ground-glass opacification, cobblestone/reticular pattern (blue arrow and blue line around region), fibrosis and dilated bronchi with thickened wall (the enlarged image in the upper right corner, red arrow). B showed consolidation (pink arrow) and mixed pattern (yellow arrow and yellow line around region) in the bilateral lower lobes.']"
Patient 82	2020.03.04.20026005-p12-1946%0.png	"['Figure 2 Chest Computed Tomographic Images of two Discharged Patients of Serious Conditions Infected With NCP. Baseline CT images at admission of the first discharged patient (IP: C56, 57 years) show multiple patchy pure ground glass opacity (GGO), GGO with reticular and/or interlobular septal thickening (A). ']"
Patient 82	2020.03.04.20026005-p12-1946%1.png	"['Figure 2 Chest Computed Tomographic Images of two Discharged Patients of Serious Conditions Infected With NCP. After the disease progressed, Follow-up CT images at 7 day show pulmonary consolidation occurred, lung parenchyma from peripheral to the central lung interstitium (B). ']"
Patient 82	2020.03.04.20026005-p12-1946%2.png	['Figure 2 Chest Computed Tomographic Images of two Discharged Patients of Serious Conditions Infected With NCP. Follow-up CT images at 21 day show most of the lesions were absorbed and some of them showed changes of pulmonary interstitial fibrosis (C). ']
Patient 83	2020.03.04.20026005-p12-1946%3.png	"['Figure 2 Chest Computed Tomographic Images of two Discharged Patients of Serious Conditions Infected With NCP. Baseline CT images at admission of the second discharged patient (IP: C54, 37years) show multiple patchy pure ground glass opacity (GGO), GGO with reticular and/or interlobular septal thickening (D). ']"
Patient 83	2020.03.04.20026005-p12-1946%4.png	"['Figure 2 Chest Computed Tomographic Images of two Discharged Patients of Serious Conditions Infected With NCP. After the disease progressed, Follow-up CT images at 9 day show pulmonary consolidation occurred, from peripheral pulmonary parenchyma to the central lung interstitium (E). ']"
Patient 83	2020.03.04.20026005-p12-1946%5.png	['Figure 2 Chest Computed Tomographic Images of two Discharged Patients of Serious Conditions Infected With NCP. Follow-up CT images at 21 day show most of the lesions were absorbed and some of them showed changes of pulmonary interstitial fibrosis (F). ']
Patient 84	2020.03.04.20030395-p27-108%0.png	['Figure 1. Representative chest CT images from multiple patients. Various radiographic abnormalities are present as follows: 1. Intralobular septal thickening and parenchymal bands in the right lower lobe.']
Patient 85	2020.03.04.20030395-p27-108%1.png	['Figure 1. Representative chest CT images from multiple patients. Various radiographic abnormalities are present as follows: 2. A small region of subpleural ground glass opacity with partial consolidation in the right lower lobe. ']
Patient 86	2020.03.04.20030395-p27-108%2.png	['Figure 1. Representative chest CT images from multiple patients. Various radiographic abnormalities are present as follows: 3. A small region of subpleural consolidation in the posterior right upper lobe.  ']
Patient 87	2020.03.04.20030395-p27-108%3.png	"['Figure 1. Representative chest CT images from multiple patients. Various radiographic abnormalities are present as follows: 4. Bilateral multilobular ground glass opacity and partial consolidation, and a pneumatocele in the right upper lobe. ']"
Patient 88	2020.03.04.20030395-p27-108%4.png	"['Figure 1. Representative chest CT images from multiple patients. Various radiographic abnormalities are present as follows: 5. Bilateral consolidation in the peripheral regions of the upper lobes, with inter- and intra-lobular septal thickening (crazy paving pattern).']"
Patient 89	2020.03.04.20030395-p27-108%5.png	"['Figure 1. Representative chest CT images from multiple patients. Various radiographic abnormalities are present as follows: 6. Bilateral consolidation in the subpleural region of lower lobes, with parenchymal bands. Air bronchograms are present in the right lower lobe.']"
Patient 90	2020.03.04.20030395-p27-108%6.png	['Figure 1. Representative chest CT images from multiple patients. Various radiographic abnormalities are present as follows: 7. Diffuse consolidation in the right lower lobe. Ground glass opacity with partial consolidation in multiple lobes of left lung.']
Patient 91	2020.03.04.20030395-p27-108%7.png	['Figure 1. Representative chest CT images from multiple patients. Various radiographic abnormalities are present as follows: 8. Bilateral diffuse consolidation with air bronchograms in the lower lobes. Multiple areas of patchy consolidation in the right middle lobe. ']
Patient 92	2020.03.04.20030395-p27-108%8.png	['Figure 1. Representative chest CT images from multiple patients. Various radiographic abnormalities are present as follows: 9. Bilateral diffuse consolidation with air bronchograms.']
Patient 93	2020.03.04.20031039-p23-97_1%0.png	"['Figure 2 A: Chest computed tomographic images obtained from a 47-year-old male patient on day 6 after symptom onset, showed extensive and fused ground glass opacity (red arrow) in both lungs.']"
Patient 93	2020.03.04.20031039-p23-97_1%1.png	"['Figure 2 A: Chest computed tomographic images obtained from a 47-year-old male patient on day 6 after symptom onset, showed extensive and fused ground glass opacity (red arrow) in both lungs.']"
Patient 93	2020.03.04.20031039-p23-97_1%2.png	"['Figure 2 A: Chest computed tomographic images obtained from a 47-year-old male patient on day 6 after symptom onset, showed extensive and fused ground glass opacity (red arrow) in both lungs.']"
Patient 94	2020.03.04.20031039-p23-97_2%0.png	"['Figure 2 B: Chest computed tomographic images obtained from a 59year-old female on day 7 after symptom onset, showed extensive and fused ground glass opacity (red arrow) in both lungs.']"
Patient 94	2020.03.04.20031039-p23-97_2%1.png	"['Figure 2 B: Chest computed tomographic images obtained from a 59year-old female on day 7 after symptom onset, showed extensive and fused ground glass opacity (red arrow) in both lungs.']"
Patient 94	2020.03.04.20031039-p23-97_2%2.png	"['Figure 2 B: Chest computed tomographic images obtained from a 59year-old female on day 7 after symptom onset, showed extensive and fused ground glass opacity (red arrow) in both lungs.']"
Patient 95	2020.03.04.20031047-p12-81%0.png	"['FIGURE 1, Typical imaging for heart failure and COVID-19 pneumonia. A, Heart failure with bilateral diffuse disease. The disease presented with a gradient distribution and partial GGO and consolidation inside, accompanied with subpleural effusion. Peribronchovascular and septal thickening were also found. ']"
Patient 96	2020.03.04.20031047-p12-81%1.png	"['FIGURE 1, Typical imaging for heart failure and COVID-19 pneumonia. B, Heart failure with bilateral diffuse GGO disease. Peribronchovascular thickening, clear interlobular septal thickening even fissural thickening were found without subpleural effusion. ']"
Patient 97	2020.03.04.20031047-p12-81%2.png	"['FIGURE 1, Typical imaging for heart failure and COVID-19 pneumonia. C, COVID-19 with single rounded subpleural GGO in left lung.']"
Patient 98	2020.03.04.20031047-p12-81%3.png	"['FIGURE 1, Typical imaging for heart failure and COVID-19 pneumonia. D, COVID-19 with rounded GGO in bilateral lungs, partial consolidation was found inside.']"
Patient 99	2020.03.04.20031047-p13-84%0.png	"['FIGURE 2, Different imaging features for heart failure and COVID-19. A, Big patchy GGO in left lung and sporadic GGO in right lung. Peribronchovascular thickening, fissural thickening (arrow) were also found with subpleural effusion.']"
Patient 100	2020.03.04.20031047-p13-84%1.png	"['FIGURE 2, Different imaging features for heart failure and COVID-19. B, Subpleural GGO with band-shaped morphology (arrow) in the dorsal segment of bilateral lungs. Interlobular septal thickening and cardiac enlargement were also found.']"
Patient 101	2020.03.04.20031047-p13-84%2.png	"['FIGURE 2, Different imaging features for heart failure and COVID-19. C, Patchy lesion of Crazy Paving Pattern in right upper lung with partial consolidation inside. Small pulmonary vein enlargement (arrow) was also found, accompanied with subpleural effusion in the right lung. ']"
Patient 102	2020.03.04.20031047-p13-84%3.png	"['FIGURE 2, Different imaging features for heart failure and COVID-19. D, Big patchy GGO in left lung. Interlobular septal thickening was also found inside.']"
Patient 103	2020.03.04.20031047-p13-84%4.png	"['FIGURE 2, Different imaging features for heart failure and COVID-19. E, Multiple disease mixed with GGO and consolidation in bilateral lungs.  Fibrous lesion (arrow) was found in the left lung.']"
Patient 104	2020.03.04.20031047-p13-84%5.png	"['FIGURE 2, Different imaging features for heart failure and COVID-19. F, Patchy lesion of Crazy Paving Pattern in left upper lung with partial consolidation inside.']"
Patient 105	2020.03.04.20031047-p14-87%0.png	"['FIGURE 3, CT imaging of a patient with both heart failure and COVID-19. A, Diffuse disease mixed with GGO and consolidation in bilateral upper lungs, accompanied with interlobular septal thickening and subpleural effusion.']"
Patient 105	2020.03.04.20031047-p14-87%1.png	"['FIGURE 3, CT imaging of a patient with both heart failure and COVID-19. B, Big patchy GGO with irregular morphology in bilateral lungs. Peribronchovascular thickening and subpleural effusion were also found. ']"
Patient 106	2020.03.07.20031393-p7-50%0.png	"['Figure 4: Chest CTs of a asymptomatic patient, obtained on Fab 10 showed small patchy high density shadows and ground glass shadows in the lower lobe of the right lung near the pleural surface.']"
Patient 106	2020.03.07.20031393-p7-50%1.png	"['Figure 4: Chest CTs of a asymptomatic patient, obtained on Fab 10 showed small patchy high density shadows and ground glass shadows in the lower lobe of the right lung near the pleural surface.']"
Patient 106	2020.03.07.20031393-p7-50%2.png	"['Figure 4: Chest CTs of a asymptomatic patient, obtained on Fab 10 showed small patchy high density shadows and ground glass shadows in the lower lobe of the right lung near the pleural surface.']"
Patient 106	2020.03.07.20031393-p7-50%3.png	"['Figure 4: Chest CTs of a asymptomatic patient, obtained on Fab 10 showed small patchy high density shadows and ground glass shadows in the lower lobe of the right lung near the pleural surface.']"
Patient 107	2020.03.08.20031658-p15-103.png	['Figure 1. Representative chest radiographic manifestations in mild and severe cases with COVID-19. ']
Patient 108	2020.03.08.20031658-p15-104.png	['Figure 1. Representative chest radiographic manifestations in mild and severe cases with COVID-19. ']
Patient 109	2020.03.08.20031658-p15-105.png	['Figure 1. Representative chest radiographic manifestations in mild and severe cases with COVID-19. ']
Patient 110	2020.03.08.20031658-p15-106.png	['Figure 1. Representative chest radiographic manifestations in mild and severe cases with COVID-19. ']
Patient 111	2020.03.09.20033118-p20-93%0.png	"['Figure 1: Transverse thin-section CT scans in medical staffs infected with COVID-19 pneumonia. (A) 27-year-old woman: bilateral, peripheral ground-glass opacity in the right lower lobe and left upper lobe (arrow).']"
Patient 112	2020.03.09.20033118-p20-93%1.png	['Figure 1: Transverse thin-section CT scans in medical staffs infected with COVID-19 pneumonia. (B) 41-year-old woman: focal ground-glass opacity associated with smooth interlobular and intralobular septal thickening (crazy-paving pattern).']
Patient 113	2020.03.09.20033118-p20-93%2.png	"['Figure 1: Transverse thin-section CT scans in medical staffs infected with COVID-19 pneumonia. (C) 55-year-old man: bilateral, peripheral ground-glass opacity mixed consolidation pattern.']"
Patient 114	2020.03.09.20033118-p20-93%3.png	"['Figure 1: Transverse thin-section CT scans in medical staffs infected with COVID-19 pneumonia. (D) 28-year-old man: bilateral and linear consolidations in the right and left upper lobes (arrow), regarded as chronic lung lesion with lack of changes on serial CT examinations.']"
Patient 115	2020.03.10.20032136-p34-118_1%0.png	"['Figure 1. Chest computed tomographic (CT) images for study patients infected with COVID-19. Panel A depicted the chest CT images for a patient aged 21 years on day 10 after illness onset, and Panel B depicted the chest CT images for a patient aged 33 years on day 14 after illness onset.']"
Patient 115	2020.03.10.20032136-p34-118_1%1.png	"['Figure 1. Chest computed tomographic (CT) images for study patients infected with COVID-19. Panel A depicted the chest CT images for a patient aged 21 years on day 10 after illness onset, and Panel B depicted the chest CT images for a patient aged 33 years on day 14 after illness onset.']"
Patient 116	2020.03.10.20032136-p34-118_2%0.png	"['Figure 1. Chest computed tomographic (CT) images for study patients infected with COVID-19. Panel A depicted the chest CT images for a patient aged 21 years on day 10 after illness onset, and Panel B depicted the chest CT images for a patient aged 33 years on day 14 after illness onset.']"
Patient 116	2020.03.10.20032136-p34-118_2%1.png	"['Figure 1. Chest computed tomographic (CT) images for study patients infected with COVID-19. Panel A depicted the chest CT images for a patient aged 21 years on day 10 after illness onset, and Panel B depicted the chest CT images for a patient aged 33 years on day 14 after illness onset.']"
Patient 117	2020.03.11.20033159-p12-45%0.png	"['Figure 1. Transverse Chest Computed Tomographic Images. CT image from case 1 on day 1 after symptom onset, showing delicate patches of ground glass opacity of lower lobe of right lung near the pleura (1A, red arrow).']"
Patient 117	2020.03.11.20033159-p12-45%1.png	"['Figure 1. Transverse Chest Computed Tomographic Images. After receiving treatment for 10 days, the lesions were completely absorbed(1B).']"
Patient 118	2020.03.11.20033159-p12-45%2.png	"['Figure 1. Transverse Chest Computed Tomographic Images. Case 2 showed ground glass consolidation of the left lower lobe near the pleura on Admission (2A, red arrow).']"
Patient 118	2020.03.11.20033159-p12-45%3.png	['Figure 1. Transverse Chest Computed Tomographic Images. Complete resolution of lesion was observed after treatment for 13 days (2B).']
Patient 119	2020.03.11.20033159-p12-45%4.png	['Figure 1. Transverse Chest Computed Tomographic Images. There was no obvious abnormality in bilateral lung fields of case 3 on admission (3A).']
Patient 119	2020.03.11.20033159-p12-45%5.png	['Figure 1. Transverse Chest Computed Tomographic Images. No change in CT imaging was observed during patient's hospitalization (3B).']
Patient 120	2020.03.12.20027185-p8-216.png	['Figure 5: Some accurate and erroneous predictions of the proposed DeCoVNet.']
Patient 121	2020.03.12.20027185-p8-217.png	['Figure 5: Some accurate and erroneous predictions of the proposed DeCoVNet.']
Patient 122	2020.03.12.20027185-p8-218.png	['Figure 5: Some accurate and erroneous predictions of the proposed DeCoVNet.']
Patient 123	2020.03.12.20027185-p8-221.png	['Figure 5: Some accurate and erroneous predictions of the proposed DeCoVNet.']
Patient 124	2020.03.12.20034686-p17-91-3.png	['Fig 2. Typical Features of CT Images of Paediatric Patients with COVID-19.']
Patient 125	2020.03.12.20034686-p17-91-4.png	['Fig 2. Typical Features of CT Images of Paediatric Patients with COVID-19.']
Patient 126	2020.03.12.20034686-p17-91-5.png	['Fig 2. Typical Features of CT Images of Paediatric Patients with COVID-19.']
Patient 127	2020.03.12.20034686-p17-91-6.png	['Fig 2. Typical Features of CT Images of Paediatric Patients with COVID-19.']
Patient 128	2020.03.13.20035212-p23-152.png	['Figure 4. The course of chest CT images of case 8. (A) Images from January 26 show bilateral pleural effusion and pericardial effusion.']
Patient 129	2020.03.13.20035212-p23-153.png	['Figure 4. The course of chest CT images of case 8. (A) Images from January 26 show bilateral pleural effusion and pericardial effusion.']
Patient 130	2020.03.13.20035212-p23-154.png	['Figure 4. The course of chest CT images of case 8. (A) Images from January 26 show bilateral pleural effusion and pericardial effusion.']
Patient 131	2020.03.13.20035212-p23-155.png	['Figure 4. The course of chest CT images of case 8. (B) Images from February 3 show bilateral pleural effusion and pericardial effusion with a small area of ground-glass opacity in the left upper lung.']
Patient 132	2020.03.13.20035212-p23-156.png	['Figure 4. The course of chest CT images of case 8. (B) Images from February 3 show bilateral pleural effusion and pericardial effusion with a small area of ground-glass opacity in the left upper lung.']
Patient 133	2020.03.13.20035212-p23-157.png	['Figure 4. The course of chest CT images of case 8. (B) Images from February 3 show bilateral pleural effusion and pericardial effusion with a small area of ground-glass opacity in the left upper lung.']
Patient 134	2020.03.13.20035212-p23-158.png	['Figure 4. The course of chest CT images of case 8. (C) Images from February 7 show increased ground-glass opacity of the left upper lung with bilateral pleural effusion. A small area of new ground-glass opacity appeared in the right lung.']
Patient 135	2020.03.13.20035212-p23-159.png	['Figure 4. The course of chest CT images of case 8. (C) Images from February 7 show increased ground-glass opacity of the left upper lung with bilateral pleural effusion. A small area of new ground-glass opacity appeared in the right lung.']
Patient 136	2020.03.13.20035212-p23-160.png	['Figure 4. The course of chest CT images of case 8. (C) Images from February 7 show increased ground-glass opacity of the left upper lung with bilateral pleural effusion. A small area of new ground-glass opacity appeared in the right lung.']
Patient 137	2020.03.13.20035212-p23-161.png	"['Figure 4. The course of chest CT images of case 8. (D) Images from February 11 show the further enlarged ground-glass opacity of the left upper lung. New ground-glass opacity is visible in the rest areas of lungs. The left pleural effusion decreased, and the right pleural effusion increased.']"
Patient 138	2020.03.13.20035212-p23-162.png	"['Figure 4. The course of chest CT images of case 8. (D) Images from February 11 show the further enlarged ground-glass opacity of the left upper lung. New ground-glass opacity is visible in the rest areas of lungs. The left pleural effusion decreased, and the right pleural effusion increased.']"
Patient 139	2020.03.13.20035212-p23-163.png	"['Figure 4. The course of chest CT images of case 8. (D) Images from February 11 show the further enlarged ground-glass opacity of the left upper lung. New ground-glass opacity is visible in the rest areas of lungs. The left pleural effusion decreased, and the right pleural effusion increased.']"
Patient 140	2020.03.16.20035105-p6-64-1.png	"['Figure 1. Chest CT imaging of the patient with COVID-19. Chest CT showed patchy high-density blurred shadow in the upper lobe of the left lung (Figure 1A) and patchy ground glass shadow in the anterior segment of the upper lobe of the right lung (Figure 1B). After treatment, chest CT showed that the previous lesions were almost absorbed. ']"
Patient 140	2020.03.16.20035105-p6-64-2.png	"['Figure 1. Chest CT imaging of the patient with COVID-19. Chest CT showed patchy high-density blurred shadow in the upper lobe of the left lung (Figure 1A) and patchy ground glass shadow in the anterior segment of the upper lobe of the right lung (Figure 1B). After treatment, chest CT showed that the previous lesions were almost absorbed. ']"
Patient 140	2020.03.16.20035105-p6-64-3.png	"['Figure 1. Chest CT imaging of the patient with COVID-19. Chest CT showed patchy high-density blurred shadow in the upper lobe of the left lung (Figure 1A) and patchy ground glass shadow in the anterior segment of the upper lobe of the right lung (Figure 1B). After treatment, chest CT showed that the previous lesions were almost absorbed. ']"
Patient 140	2020.03.16.20035105-p6-64-4.png	"['Figure 1. Chest CT imaging of the patient with COVID-19. Chest CT showed patchy high-density blurred shadow in the upper lobe of the left lung (Figure 1A) and patchy ground glass shadow in the anterior segment of the upper lobe of the right lung (Figure 1B). After treatment, chest CT showed that the previous lesions were almost absorbed. ']"
Patient 141	2020.03.16.20036145-p19-128-1.png	['Figure 1.Chest CTs of two patients (A) Chest CT of patient 9 obtained on Feb 9 (7 dpoi) before convalescent plasma transfusion (10 dpoi)showed ground glass opacity with uneven density involving the multilobal segments of both lungs. The heart shadow outline was not clear. The lesion was close to the pleura.']
Patient 141	2020.03.16.20036145-p19-128-2.png	['Figure 1.Chest CTs of two patients (B) CT Image of patient 9 taken on Feb 15(13 dpoi) showed the absorption of bilateral ground glassopacity after convalescent plasma transfusion. ']
Patient 142	2020.03.16.20036145-p19-128-3.png	['Figure 1.Chest CTs of two patients (C)Chest CT of patient 10 was obtained on Feb 8 (19 dpoi) before convalescent plasma transfusion (20 dpoi). The brightness of both lungs was diffusely decreased and multiple shadows of high density in both lungs were observed. ']
Patient 142	2020.03.16.20036145-p19-128-4.png	['Figure 1.Chest CTs of two patients (D) Chest CTof patient 10 on Feb 18 (29dpoi) showed those lesions improvedafter convalescent plasma transfusion. ']
Patient 143	2020.03.18.20038125-p15-54-1.png	"['Figure 1. The CT pattern of abnormal lung findings among asymptomatic patients with COVID-19. A patient 73 years old, female. The patchy non-segmental ground grass opacity (GGO) adjacent to the parietal pleura in the right upper lobe (A and B), and in both lower lobes (C and D). ']"
Patient 143	2020.03.18.20038125-p15-54-2.png	"['Figure 1. The CT pattern of abnormal lung findings among asymptomatic patients with COVID-19. A patient 73 years old, female. The patchy non-segmental ground grass opacity (GGO) adjacent to the parietal pleura in the right upper lobe (A and B), and in both lower lobes (C and D). ']"
Patient 143	2020.03.18.20038125-p15-54-3.png	"['Figure 1. The CT pattern of abnormal lung findings among asymptomatic patients with COVID-19. A patient 73 years old, female. The patchy non-segmental ground grass opacity (GGO) adjacent to the parietal pleura in the right upper lobe (A and B), and in both lower lobes (C and D). ']"
Patient 143	2020.03.18.20038125-p15-54-4.png	"['Figure 1. The CT pattern of abnormal lung findings among asymptomatic patients with COVID-19. A patient 73 years old, female. The patchy non-segmental ground grass opacity (GGO) adjacent to the parietal pleura in the right upper lobe (A and B), and in both lower lobes (C and D). ']"
Patient 143	2020.03.18.20038125-p15-54-5.png	"['Figure 1. The CT pattern of abnormal lung findings among asymptomatic patients with COVID-19. A patient 70 years old, female. The GGO with interlobular septal thickening (crazy-paving appearance) adjacent to the parietal pleura in the both lower lobes (E).']"
Patient 143	2020.03.18.20038125-p15-54-6.png	"['Figure 1. The CT pattern of abnormal lung findings among asymptomatic patients with COVID-19. A patient 76 years old, male. CT scan showed the GGO with consolidation, bronchial wall thickening, and bronchiectasis in the left lower lobe (F).']"
Patient 144	2020.03.18.20038125-p16-56-1.png	"['Figure 2. The progress of CT findings in a patient with COVID-19. A male patient 75 years old was asymptomatic on the admission day. On the fourth day of admission, he showed tachypnea and hypoxemia, and treated oxygen therapy. On the admission day, Chest CT scan showed multifocal GGO adjacent to the parietal pleura in multiple lobes with emphysematous changes (A, B and C).']"
Patient 144	2020.03.18.20038125-p16-56-2.png	"['Figure 2. The progress of CT findings in a patient with COVID-19. A male patient 75 years old was asymptomatic on the admission day. On the fourth day of admission, he showed tachypnea and hypoxemia, and treated oxygen therapy. On the admission day, Chest CT scan showed multifocal GGO adjacent to the parietal pleura in multiple lobes with emphysematous changes (A, B and C).']"
Patient 144	2020.03.18.20038125-p16-56-3.png	"['Figure 2. The progress of CT findings in a patient with COVID-19. A male patient 75 years old was asymptomatic on the admission day. On the fourth day of admission, he showed tachypnea and hypoxemia, and treated oxygen therapy. On the admission day, Chest CT scan showed multifocal GGO adjacent to the parietal pleura in multiple lobes with emphysematous changes (A, B and C).']"
Patient 144	2020.03.18.20038125-p16-56-4.png	"['Figure 2. The progress of CT findings in a patient with COVID-19. On the tenth day of admission, a follow-up chest CT scan showed an increase of extent of GGO with crazy-paving appearance (D, E and F).']"
Patient 144	2020.03.18.20038125-p16-56-5.png	"['Figure 2. The progress of CT findings in a patient with COVID-19. On the tenth day of admission, a follow-up chest CT scan showed an increase of extent of GGO with crazy-paving appearance (D, E and F).']"
Patient 144	2020.03.18.20038125-p16-56-6.png	"['Figure 2. The progress of CT findings in a patient with COVID-19. On the tenth day of admission, a follow-up chest CT scan showed an increase of extent of GGO with crazy-paving appearance (D, E and F).']"
Patient 145	2020.03.19.20038539-p10-57.png	['Figure 2. Chest Computed Tomographic Images of a 50-Year-Old Severe Patient Infected With Coronavirus Disease 2019. ']
Patient 145	2020.03.19.20038539-p10-58.png	['Figure 2. Chest Computed Tomographic Images of a 50-Year-Old Severe Patient Infected With Coronavirus Disease 2019. ']
Patient 145	2020.03.19.20038539-p10-59.png	['Figure 2. Chest Computed Tomographic Images of a 50-Year-Old Severe Patient Infected With Coronavirus Disease 2019. ']
Patient 145	2020.03.19.20038539-p10-60.png	['Figure 2. Chest Computed Tomographic Images of a 50-Year-Old Severe Patient Infected With Coronavirus Disease 2019. ']
Patient 145	2020.03.19.20038539-p10-61.png	['Figure 2. Chest Computed Tomographic Images of a 50-Year-Old Severe Patient Infected With Coronavirus Disease 2019. ']
Patient 145	2020.03.19.20038539-p10-62.png	['Figure 2. Chest Computed Tomographic Images of a 50-Year-Old Severe Patient Infected With Coronavirus Disease 2019. ']
Patient 146	2020.03.20.20037325-p23-121.png	"['Figure 4: Representative cases without malignant progression (A, B) and with malignant']"
Patient 147	2020.03.20.20037325-p23-122.png	"['Figure 4: Representative cases without malignant progression (A, B) and with malignant']"
Patient 148	2020.03.20.20037325-p23-123.png	"['Figure 4: Representative cases without malignant progression (A, B) and with malignant']"
Patient 149	2020.03.20.20037325-p23-124.png	"['Figure 4: Representative cases without malignant progression (A, B) and with malignant']"
Patient 150	2020.03.21.20040691-p18-6-6.png	"['Figure 4: Chest CT image. Transverse chest CT images from a 65-year-old male patient showing bilateral large flaky ground glass shadows and consolidation on baseline period. At day 22, the intrapulmonary lesions were significantly absorbed and dissipated by meplazumab addon treatment. ']"
Patient 150	2020.03.21.20040691-p18-67-1.png	"['Figure 4: Chest CT image. Transverse chest CT images from a 65-year-old male patient showing bilateral large flaky ground glass shadows and consolidation on baseline period. At day 22, the intrapulmonary lesions were significantly absorbed and dissipated by meplazumab addon treatment. ']"
Patient 150	2020.03.21.20040691-p18-67-2.png	"['Figure 4: Chest CT image. Transverse chest CT images from a 65-year-old male patient showing bilateral large flaky ground glass shadows and consolidation on baseline period. At day 22, the intrapulmonary lesions were significantly absorbed and dissipated by meplazumab addon treatment. ']"
Patient 150	2020.03.21.20040691-p18-67-3.png	"['Figure 4: Chest CT image. Transverse chest CT images from a 65-year-old male patient showing bilateral large flaky ground glass shadows and consolidation on baseline period. At day 22, the intrapulmonary lesions were significantly absorbed and dissipated by meplazumab addon treatment. ']"
Patient 150	2020.03.21.20040691-p18-67-4.png	"['Figure 4: Chest CT image. Transverse chest CT images from a 65-year-old male patient showing bilateral large flaky ground glass shadows and consolidation on baseline period. At day 22, the intrapulmonary lesions were significantly absorbed and dissipated by meplazumab addon treatment. ']"
Patient 150	2020.03.21.20040691-p18-67-5.png	"['Figure 4: Chest CT image. Transverse chest CT images from a 65-year-old male patient showing bilateral large flaky ground glass shadows and consolidation on baseline period. At day 22, the intrapulmonary lesions were significantly absorbed and dissipated by meplazumab addon treatment. ']"
Patient 150	2020.03.21.20040691-p18-67-7.png	"['Figure 4: Chest CT image. Transverse chest CT images from a 65-year-old male patient showing bilateral large flaky ground glass shadows and consolidation on baseline period. At day 22, the intrapulmonary lesions were significantly absorbed and dissipated by meplazumab addon treatment. ']"
Patient 150	2020.03.21.20040691-p18-67-8.png	"['Figure 4: Chest CT image. Transverse chest CT images from a 65-year-old male patient showing bilateral large flaky ground glass shadows and consolidation on baseline period. At day 22, the intrapulmonary lesions were significantly absorbed and dissipated by meplazumab addon treatment. ']"
Patient 151	2020.03.22.20034041-p16-66.png	['Figure 2 Natural patient receiving danoprevir/ritonavir plus interferon nebulization (Patient 1)  ']
Patient 152	2020.03.22.20034041-p17-80-1.png	['Figure 3 Experienced patient treated with lopinavir/ritonavir plus interferon nebulization for 3 days and switched to danoprevir/ritonavir plus interferon nebulization. ']
Patient 152	2020.03.22.20034041-p17-80-2.png	['Figure 3 Experienced patient treated with lopinavir/ritonavir plus interferon nebulization for 3 days and switched to danoprevir/ritonavir plus interferon nebulization. ']
Patient 153	2020.03.22.20034041-p18-92-1.png	"['Figure 4 Patient failed lopinavir/ritonavir plus interferon nebulization and switched to danoprevir/ritonavir without interferon nebulization (Patient 8) GGO, ground-glass opacity. Red arrows indicate the possible lesions. * Viral RNA was undetectable in both nasal and phlegm swabs. ']"
Patient 153	2020.03.22.20034041-p18-92-2.png	"['Figure 4 Patient failed lopinavir/ritonavir plus interferon nebulization and switched to danoprevir/ritonavir without interferon nebulization (Patient 8) GGO, ground-glass opacity. Red arrows indicate the possible lesions. * Viral RNA was undetectable in both nasal and phlegm swabs. ']"
Patient 153	2020.03.22.20034041-p18-92-3.png	"['Figure 4 Patient failed lopinavir/ritonavir plus interferon nebulization and switched to danoprevir/ritonavir without interferon nebulization (Patient 8) GGO, ground-glass opacity. Red arrows indicate the possible lesions. * Viral RNA was undetectable in both nasal and phlegm swabs. ']"
Patient 154	2020.03.22.20040782-p24-1533-1.png	"['Figure 1 Various chest CT imaging features of COVID-19 GGO, ground glass opacity A, GGO with bilateral and subpleural distribution']"
Patient 155	2020.03.22.20040782-p24-1533-2.png	"['Figure 1 Various chest CT imaging features of COVID-19 GGO, ground glass opacity B, crazy-paving pattern with subpleural and bilateral lower pulmonary distribution']"
Patient 156	2020.03.22.20040782-p24-1533-3.png	"['Figure 1 Various chest CT imaging features of COVID-19 GGO, ground glass opacity C, GGO']"
Patient 157	2020.03.22.20040782-p24-1533-4.png	"['Figure 1 Various chest CT imaging features of COVID-19 GGO, ground glass opacity D, GGO with bilateral and subpleural distribution']"
Patient 158	2020.03.22.20040782-p24-1533-5.png	"['Figure 1 Various chest CT imaging features of COVID-19 GGO, ground glass opacity E, GGO with crazy-paving pattern and air bronchogram']"
Patient 159	2020.03.22.20040782-p24-1533-6.png	"['Figure 1 Various chest CT imaging features of COVID-19 GGO, ground glass opacity F, GGO with consolidation']"
Patient 160	2020.03.22.20040782-p24-1533-7.png	"['Figure 1 Various chest CT imaging features of COVID-19 GGO, ground glass opacity G, GGO with air bronchogram and subpleural distribution']"
Patient 161	2020.03.22.20040782-p24-1533-8.png	"['Figure 1 Various chest CT imaging features of COVID-19 GGO, ground glass opacity H, GGO with unilateral and subpleural distribution']"
Patient 162	2020.03.22.20040782-p25-1541.png	"['Figure 1 Various chest CT imaging features of COVID-19 GGO, ground glass opacity ']"
Patient 163	2020.03.22.20040782-p25-1542.png	"['Figure 1 Various chest CT imaging features of COVID-19 GGO, ground glass opacity ']"
Patient 164	2020.03.22.20040782-p25-1543.png	"['Figure 1 Various chest CT imaging features of COVID-19 GGO, ground glass opacity ']"
Patient 165	2020.03.22.20040782-p25-1544.png	"['Figure 1 Various chest CT imaging features of COVID-19 GGO, ground glass opacity ']"
Patient 166	2020.03.22.20040782-p25-1545.png	"['Figure 1 Various chest CT imaging features of COVID-19 GGO, ground glass opacity ']"
Patient 167	2020.03.22.20040782-p25-1546.png	"['Figure 1 Various chest CT imaging features of COVID-19 GGO, ground glass opacity ']"