2020.01.24.919183-p27-132.png	"['Figure 1. Chest radiographs of patient 1. a. b. c. d. Chest computed tomographic scans of Patient 1 were obtained on the day of admission (day 6 after the onset of illness). Bilateral focal consolidation, lobar consolidation, and patchy consolidation were clearly observed, especially in the lower lung. ']"
2020.01.24.919183-p27-133.png	"['Figure 1. Chest radiographs of patient 1. a. b. c. d. Chest computed tomographic scans of Patient 1 were obtained on the day of admission (day 6 after the onset of illness). Bilateral focal consolidation, lobar consolidation, and patchy consolidation were clearly observed, especially in the lower lung. ']"
2020.01.24.919183-p27-134.png	"['Figure 1. Chest radiographs of patient 1. a. b. c. d. Chest computed tomographic scans of Patient 1 were obtained on the day of admission (day 6 after the onset of illness). Bilateral focal consolidation, lobar consolidation, and patchy consolidation were clearly observed, especially in the lower lung. ']"
2020.01.24.919183-p27-135.png	"['Figure 1. Chest radiographs of patient 1. a. b. c. d. Chest computed tomographic scans of Patient 1 were obtained on the day of admission (day 6 after the onset of illness). Bilateral focal consolidation, lobar consolidation, and patchy consolidation were clearly observed, especially in the lower lung. ']"
2020.02.10.20021584-p6-52%0.png	"['Figure 1. A 50-year-old man with 2019 novel coronavirus (2019-nCoV) infection. (A) Ground glass shadow in multiple lobes and segments of bilateral lungs, and the lesions were adjacent to the pleura (Illness Day 8, Hospital Day 0). ']"
2020.02.10.20021584-p6-52%1.png	"['Figure 1. A 50-year-old man with 2019 novel coronavirus (2019-nCoV) infection. (A) Ground glass shadow in multiple lobes and segments of bilateral lungs, and the lesions were adjacent to the pleura (Illness Day 8, Hospital Day 0). ']"
2020.02.10.20021584-p6-52%10.png	"['Figure 1. A 50-year-old man with 2019 novel coronavirus (2019-nCoV) infection. (C) Ground glass shadow absorption and reduced consolidation area (Illness Day 15, Hospital Day 7).']"
2020.02.10.20021584-p6-52%11.png	"['Figure 1. A 50-year-old man with 2019 novel coronavirus (2019-nCoV) infection. (C) Ground glass shadow absorption and reduced consolidation area (Illness Day 15, Hospital Day 7).']"
2020.02.10.20021584-p6-52%12.png	"['Figure 1. A 50-year-old man with 2019 novel coronavirus (2019-nCoV) infection. (D) Lesion dissipation (Illness Day 20, Hospital Day 12). ']"
2020.02.10.20021584-p6-52%13.png	"['Figure 1. A 50-year-old man with 2019 novel coronavirus (2019-nCoV) infection. (D) Lesion dissipation (Illness Day 20, Hospital Day 12). ']"
2020.02.10.20021584-p6-52%14.png	"['Figure 1. A 50-year-old man with 2019 novel coronavirus (2019-nCoV) infection. (D) Lesion dissipation (Illness Day 20, Hospital Day 12). ']"
2020.02.10.20021584-p6-52%15.png	"['Figure 1. A 50-year-old man with 2019 novel coronavirus (2019-nCoV) infection. (D) Lesion dissipation (Illness Day 20, Hospital Day 12). ']"
2020.02.10.20021584-p6-52%2.png	"['Figure 1. A 50-year-old man with 2019 novel coronavirus (2019-nCoV) infection. (A) Ground glass shadow in multiple lobes and segments of bilateral lungs, and the lesions were adjacent to the pleura (Illness Day 8, Hospital Day 0). ']"
2020.02.10.20021584-p6-52%3.png	"['Figure 1. A 50-year-old man with 2019 novel coronavirus (2019-nCoV) infection. (A) Ground glass shadow in multiple lobes and segments of bilateral lungs, and the lesions were adjacent to the pleura (Illness Day 8, Hospital Day 0). ']"
2020.02.10.20021584-p6-52%4.png	"['Figure 1. A 50-year-old man with 2019 novel coronavirus (2019-nCoV) infection. (B) Ground glass shadow expanding and consolidation in bilateral lung (Illness Day 11, Hospital Day 3). ']"
2020.02.10.20021584-p6-52%5.png	"['Figure 1. A 50-year-old man with 2019 novel coronavirus (2019-nCoV) infection. (B) Ground glass shadow expanding and consolidation in bilateral lung (Illness Day 11, Hospital Day 3). ']"
2020.02.10.20021584-p6-52%6.png	"['Figure 1. A 50-year-old man with 2019 novel coronavirus (2019-nCoV) infection. (B) Ground glass shadow expanding and consolidation in bilateral lung (Illness Day 11, Hospital Day 3). ']"
2020.02.10.20021584-p6-52%7.png	"['Figure 1. A 50-year-old man with 2019 novel coronavirus (2019-nCoV) infection. (B) Ground glass shadow expanding and consolidation in bilateral lung (Illness Day 11, Hospital Day 3). ']"
2020.02.10.20021584-p6-52%8.png	"['Figure 1. A 50-year-old man with 2019 novel coronavirus (2019-nCoV) infection. (C) Ground glass shadow absorption and reduced consolidation area (Illness Day 15, Hospital Day 7).']"
2020.02.10.20021584-p6-52%9.png	"['Figure 1. A 50-year-old man with 2019 novel coronavirus (2019-nCoV) infection. (C) Ground glass shadow absorption and reduced consolidation area (Illness Day 15, Hospital Day 7).']"
2020.02.11.20021493-p16-109%0.png	"['Figure 2. Computed tomography (CT) scan of the cases 02, 07 and 13.']"
2020.02.11.20021493-p16-109%1.png	"['Figure 2. Computed tomography (CT) scan of the cases 02, 07 and 13.']"
2020.02.11.20021493-p16-109%2.png	"['Figure 2. Computed tomography (CT) scan of the cases 02, 07 and 13.']"
2020.02.11.20022053-p12-67%0.png	"['Figure. Chest Computed tomography (CT) images of patients infected with 2019-nCoV on admission to hospital. A, Chest CT scan obtained on February 2, 2020, from a 39-year-old man, showing bilateral ground glass opacities.']"
2020.02.11.20022053-p12-67%1.png	"['Figure. Chest Computed tomography (CT) images of patients infected with 2019-nCoV on admission to hospital. B, Chest CT scan obtained on February 6, 2020, from a 45-year-old man, showing bilateral ground glass opacities.']"
2020.02.11.20022053-p12-67%2.png	"['Figure. Chest Computed tomography (CT) images of patients infected with 2019-nCoV on admission to hospital. C, Chest CT scan taken on January 27, 2020, from a 48-year-old man (discharged after treatment on day 9), showing patchy shadows.']"
2020.02.11.20022053-p12-67%3.png	"['Figure. Chest Computed tomography (CT) images of patients infected with 2019-nCoV on admission to hospital. D, Chest CT scan taken on January 23, 2020, from a 34-year-old man (discharged after treatment on day 11), showing patchy shadows.']"
2020.02.13.20022673-p13-77%0.png	['Figure 2. Chest computed tomographic Images of patients with SARS-CoV-2 and other pathogens. ']
2020.02.13.20022673-p13-77%1.png	['Figure 2. Chest computed tomographic Images of patients with SARS-CoV-2 and other pathogens. ']
2020.02.13.20022673-p13-77%2.png	['Figure 2. Chest computed tomographic Images of patients with SARS-CoV-2 and other pathogens. ']
2020.02.17.20024018-p17-61%0.png	['The Imageology change with the disease progression of a 36 years-old female severe patient infected with 2019-CoV A and B were second day of the course of disease; C and D were day 7; E was day 11 and F was day 15. A. CT showed local ground glass shadow and nodules.']
2020.02.17.20024018-p17-61%1.png	['The Imageology change with the disease progression of a 36 years-old female severe patient infected with 2019-CoV A and B were second day of the course of disease; C and D were day 7; E was day 11 and F was day 15. B. Thin ground glass shadow Mainly distributed in outer zone of the lung and under the pleura.']
2020.02.17.20024018-p17-61%2.png	"['The Imageology change with the disease progression of a 36 years-old female severe patient infected with 2019-CoV A and B were second day of the course of disease; C and D were day 7; E was day 11 and F was day 15. C. Ground glass shadow of both lungs, left pulmonary nodule focus located under pleura.']"
2020.02.17.20024018-p17-61%3.png	['The Imageology change with the disease progression of a 36 years-old female severe patient infected with 2019-CoV A and B were second day of the course of disease; C and D were day 7; E was day 11 and F was day 15. D. Progress to patchy shadow with uneven density.']
2020.02.17.20024018-p17-61%4.png	"['The Imageology change with the disease progression of a 36 years-old female severe patient infected with 2019-CoV A and B were second day of the course of disease; C and D were day 7; E was day 11 and F was day 15. E. Multiple patchy shadows with fuzzy edges were observed, and large ground glass shadow and condensation shadow were found in both lower lobe.']"
2020.02.19.20025023-p20-93%0.png	['Figure 1. Chest computed tomographic images of patients with coronavirus disease 2019 (A) Mild pneumonia patient showed patchy ground-glass opacity with clear borderline in a transverse chest CT image.']
2020.02.19.20025023-p20-93%1.png	['Figure 1. Chest computed tomographic images of patients with coronavirus disease 2019 (B-C) Transverse chest CT images of moderate patients showing large ground-glass opacities and some with ambiguous borderline.']
2020.02.19.20025023-p20-93%2.png	['Figure 1. Chest computed tomographic images of patients with coronavirus disease 2019 (B-C) Transverse chest CT images of moderate patients showing large ground-glass opacities and some with ambiguous borderline.']
2020.02.19.20025023-p20-93%3.png	['Figure 1. Chest computed tomographic images of patients with coronavirus disease 2019 (D) Severe cases were characterized by typical white lung change as high-density mass shadows and multiple lobular consolidations were observed.']
2020.02.22.20024927-p18-66%0.png	"['A sample scoring on CT images of a 63-year-old woman from mortality group demonstrated a total score of 63. It was calculated as: for upper zone (A), 3 (consolidation) × 3 (50-75% distribution) × 2 (both right and left lungs) + 2 (ground glass opacity) ×1 (< 25% distribution) × 2 (both right and left lungs); for middle zone. ']"
2020.02.22.20024927-p18-66%1.png	"['A sample scoring on CT images of a 63-year-old woman from mortality group demonstrated a total score of 63. It was calculated as: for upper zone (B), 3 (consolidation) × 2 (25-50% distribution) × 2 (both right and left lungs) + 2 (ground glass opacity) × 2 (25-50% distribution) × 2 (both right and left lungs) ; for lower zone. ']"
2020.02.22.20024927-p18-66%2.png	"['A sample scoring on CT images of a 63-year-old woman from mortality group demonstrated a total score of 63. It was calculated as: for upper zone (C), 3 (consolidation) × (2 (25-50% distribution of the right lung) + 3 (50-75% distribution of the left lung))  + 2 (ground glass opacity) × (2 (25-50% distribution of the right lung) + 1 (< 25% distribution of the left lung)). ']"
2020.02.22.20024927-p19-68%0.png	['CT images of a 76-year-old woman from survival group showed pure ground glass opacities with predominant peripheral distribution in middle and lower lung zones (A-C).']
2020.02.22.20024927-p19-68%1.png	['CT images of a 76-year-old woman from survival group showed pure ground glass opacities with predominant peripheral distribution in middle and lower lung zones (A-C).']
2020.02.22.20024927-p19-68%2.png	['CT images of a 76-year-old woman from survival group showed pure ground glass opacities with predominant peripheral distribution in middle and lower lung zones (A-C).']
2020.02.22.20024927-p19-68%3.png	"['Air bronchogram, together with extensive of consolidations and ground glass opacities were found in the CT images of a 72–year-old woman from mortality group (D-F).']"
2020.02.22.20024927-p19-68%4.png	"['Air bronchogram, together with extensive of consolidations and ground glass opacities were found in the CT images of a 72–year-old woman from mortality group (D-F).']"
2020.02.22.20024927-p19-68%5.png	"['Air bronchogram, together with extensive of consolidations and ground glass opacities were found in the CT images of a 72–year-old woman from mortality group (D-F).']"
2020.02.22.20024927-p20-70%0.png	['Two cases of CT images from survival group showed ground glass nodular opacities on admission and progressed to multiple patchy ground glass opacities on reexamination. The CT images of a 60-year-old woman on admission showed peripherally distributed focal ground glass nodular opacities in only right lung (A) and rechecked CT images showed expanded area of patchy ground glass opacities in both right and left lungs with reticular and interlobular septal thickening on 7 days later (B). ']
2020.02.22.20024927-p20-70%1.png	['Two cases of CT images from survival group showed ground glass nodular opacities on admission and progressed to multiple patchy ground glass opacities on reexamination. The CT images of a 60-year-old woman on admission showed peripherally distributed focal ground glass nodular opacities in only right lung (A) and rechecked CT images showed expanded area of patchy ground glass opacities in both right and left lungs with reticular and interlobular septal thickening on 7 days later (B). ']
2020.02.22.20024927-p20-70%2.png	['Two cases of CT images from survival group showed ground glass nodular opacities on admission and progressed to multiple patchy ground glass opacities on reexamination. Unilateral ground glass nodular opacity was found on CT images of a 64-year-old man from survival group (C) and progressed patchy ground glass opacities as well as interlobular septal thickening were seen after 4 days (D). ']
2020.02.22.20024927-p20-70%3.png	['Two cases of CT images from survival group showed ground glass nodular opacities on admission and progressed to multiple patchy ground glass opacities on reexamination. Unilateral ground glass nodular opacity was found on CT images of a 64-year-old man from survival group (C) and progressed patchy ground glass opacities as well as interlobular septal thickening were seen after 4 days (D). ']
2020.02.23.20026856-p17-115%0.png	"['Figure 1. Transverse chest CT from a 39 year-old man, showing ground-glass opacities of bilateral lungs near the pleura (a and b) on day 1 from symptom onset, and increased bilateral ground-glass opacities and consolidation(c and d) on day 5  from symptom onset, and slightly absorbed ground-glass opacities (e and f) on day 7 from symptom onset after 7-day treatment.']"
2020.02.23.20026856-p17-115%1.png	"['Figure 1. Transverse chest CT from a 39 year-old man, showing ground-glass opacities of bilateral lungs near the pleura (a and b) on day 1 from symptom onset, and increased bilateral ground-glass opacities and consolidation(c and d) on day 5  from symptom onset, and slightly absorbed ground-glass opacities (e and f) on day 7 from symptom onset after 7-day treatment.']"
2020.02.23.20026856-p17-115%2.png	"['Figure 1. Transverse chest CT from a 39 year-old man, showing ground-glass opacities of bilateral lungs near the pleura (a and b) on day 1 from symptom onset, and increased bilateral ground-glass opacities and consolidation(c and d) on day 5  from symptom onset, and slightly absorbed ground-glass opacities (e and f) on day 7 from symptom onset after 7-day treatment.']"
2020.02.23.20026856-p17-115%3.png	"['Figure 1. Transverse chest CT from a 39 year-old man, showing ground-glass opacities of bilateral lungs near the pleura (a and b) on day 1 from symptom onset, and increased bilateral ground-glass opacities and consolidation(c and d) on day 5  from symptom onset, and slightly absorbed ground-glass opacities (e and f) on day 7 from symptom onset after 7-day treatment.']"
2020.02.23.20026856-p17-115%4.png	"['Figure 1. Transverse chest CT from a 39 year-old man, showing ground-glass opacities of bilateral lungs near the pleura (a and b) on day 1 from symptom onset, and increased bilateral ground-glass opacities and consolidation(c and d) on day 5  from symptom onset, and slightly absorbed ground-glass opacities (e and f) on day 7 from symptom onset after 7-day treatment.']"
2020.02.23.20026856-p17-115%5.png	"['Figure 1. Transverse chest CT from a 39 year-old man, showing ground-glass opacities of bilateral lungs near the pleura (a and b) on day 1 from symptom onset, and increased bilateral ground-glass opacities and consolidation(c and d) on day 5  from symptom onset, and slightly absorbed ground-glass opacities (e and f) on day 7 from symptom onset after 7-day treatment.']"
2020.02.24.20027052-p8-73%0.png	"['Figure 4. Quantification of EAT density by CT scan. CT scan examples of the patients from light (a), mild (b), severe (c) and critical (d) group of COVID-19 patients. Dark red areas represent the EATs, and blue areas indicate other heart tissues. Red arrows indicate lung lesions, and ground-glass opacity features are obviously presented in severe (c) and critical (d) groups (marked with red arrow). Scale bar, 10 cm. ']"
2020.02.24.20027052-p8-73%1.png	"['Figure 4. Quantification of EAT density by CT scan. CT scan examples of the patients from light (a), mild (b), severe (c) and critical (d) group of COVID-19 patients. Dark red areas represent the EATs, and blue areas indicate other heart tissues. Red arrows indicate lung lesions, and ground-glass opacity features are obviously presented in severe (c) and critical (d) groups (marked with red arrow). Scale bar, 10 cm. ']"
2020.02.24.20027052-p8-73%2.png	"['Figure 4. Quantification of EAT density by CT scan. CT scan examples of the patients from light (a), mild (b), severe (c) and critical (d) group of COVID-19 patients. Dark red areas represent the EATs, and blue areas indicate other heart tissues. Red arrows indicate lung lesions, and ground-glass opacity features are obviously presented in severe (c) and critical (d) groups (marked with red arrow). Scale bar, 10 cm. ']"
2020.02.24.20027052-p8-73%3.png	"['Figure 4. Quantification of EAT density by CT scan. CT scan examples of the patients from light (a), mild (b), severe (c) and critical (d) group of COVID-19 patients. Dark red areas represent the EATs, and blue areas indicate other heart tissues. Red arrows indicate lung lesions, and ground-glass opacity features are obviously presented in severe (c) and critical (d) groups (marked with red arrow). Scale bar, 10 cm. ']"
2020.02.24.20027201-p19-669.png	['Figure 3. Representative images of chest CT scans (the transverse plane). Patients with COVID-19 had unilateral or bilateral pneumonia. The multiple “ground-glass” lesions were the characteristics of COVID-19 pneumonia.The green arrows represent the sites of lesions.']
2020.02.24.20027201-p19-670.png	['Figure 3. Representative images of chest CT scans (the transverse plane). Patients with COVID-19 had unilateral or bilateral pneumonia. The multiple “ground-glass” lesions were the characteristics of COVID-19 pneumonia.The green arrows represent the sites of lesions.']
2020.02.25.20021568-p23-108%0.png	"['Figure 3. Processing and prediction schematic of the model. Raw images were firstly input into the model, and after processing of the model, prediction boxes framing suspicious lesions were output. Valid areas were further extracted and unnecessary fields were filter out to avoid possible false positives. To predict by case, a logic linking the prediction results of consecutive images was added. Computed tomography (CT) images with the above prediction results were divided into four quadrants, and results would be output only when three consecutive images were predicted to have lesions in the same quadrant. ']"
2020.02.25.20021568-p23-108%1.png	"['Figure 3. Processing and prediction schematic of the model. Raw images were firstly input into the model, and after processing of the model, prediction boxes framing suspicious lesions were output. Valid areas were further extracted and unnecessary fields were filter out to avoid possible false positives. To predict by case, a logic linking the prediction results of consecutive images was added. Computed tomography (CT) images with the above prediction results were divided into four quadrants, and results would be output only when three consecutive images were predicted to have lesions in the same quadrant. ']"
2020.02.25.20021568-p23-108%10.png	"['Figure 3. Processing and prediction schematic of the model. Raw images were firstly input into the model, and after processing of the model, prediction boxes framing suspicious lesions were output. Valid areas were further extracted and unnecessary fields were filter out to avoid possible false positives. To predict by case, a logic linking the prediction results of consecutive images was added. Computed tomography (CT) images with the above prediction results were divided into four quadrants, and results would be output only when three consecutive images were predicted to have lesions in the same quadrant. ']"
2020.02.25.20021568-p23-108%11.png	"['Figure 3. Processing and prediction schematic of the model. Raw images were firstly input into the model, and after processing of the model, prediction boxes framing suspicious lesions were output. Valid areas were further extracted and unnecessary fields were filter out to avoid possible false positives. To predict by case, a logic linking the prediction results of consecutive images was added. Computed tomography (CT) images with the above prediction results were divided into four quadrants, and results would be output only when three consecutive images were predicted to have lesions in the same quadrant. ']"
2020.02.25.20021568-p23-108%12.png	"['Figure 3. Processing and prediction schematic of the model. Raw images were firstly input into the model, and after processing of the model, prediction boxes framing suspicious lesions were output. Valid areas were further extracted and unnecessary fields were filter out to avoid possible false positives. To predict by case, a logic linking the prediction results of consecutive images was added. Computed tomography (CT) images with the above prediction results were divided into four quadrants, and results would be output only when three consecutive images were predicted to have lesions in the same quadrant. ']"
2020.02.25.20021568-p23-108%13.png	"['Figure 3. Processing and prediction schematic of the model. Raw images were firstly input into the model, and after processing of the model, prediction boxes framing suspicious lesions were output. Valid areas were further extracted and unnecessary fields were filter out to avoid possible false positives. To predict by case, a logic linking the prediction results of consecutive images was added. Computed tomography (CT) images with the above prediction results were divided into four quadrants, and results would be output only when three consecutive images were predicted to have lesions in the same quadrant. ']"
2020.02.25.20021568-p23-108%14.png	"['Figure 3. Processing and prediction schematic of the model. Raw images were firstly input into the model, and after processing of the model, prediction boxes framing suspicious lesions were output. Valid areas were further extracted and unnecessary fields were filter out to avoid possible false positives. To predict by case, a logic linking the prediction results of consecutive images was added. Computed tomography (CT) images with the above prediction results were divided into four quadrants, and results would be output only when three consecutive images were predicted to have lesions in the same quadrant. ']"
2020.02.25.20021568-p23-108%15.png	"['Figure 3. Processing and prediction schematic of the model. Raw images were firstly input into the model, and after processing of the model, prediction boxes framing suspicious lesions were output. Valid areas were further extracted and unnecessary fields were filter out to avoid possible false positives. To predict by case, a logic linking the prediction results of consecutive images was added. Computed tomography (CT) images with the above prediction results were divided into four quadrants, and results would be output only when three consecutive images were predicted to have lesions in the same quadrant. ']"
2020.02.25.20021568-p23-108%2.png	"['Figure 3. Processing and prediction schematic of the model. Raw images were firstly input into the model, and after processing of the model, prediction boxes framing suspicious lesions were output. Valid areas were further extracted and unnecessary fields were filter out to avoid possible false positives. To predict by case, a logic linking the prediction results of consecutive images was added. Computed tomography (CT) images with the above prediction results were divided into four quadrants, and results would be output only when three consecutive images were predicted to have lesions in the same quadrant. ']"
2020.02.25.20021568-p23-108%3.png	"['Figure 3. Processing and prediction schematic of the model. Raw images were firstly input into the model, and after processing of the model, prediction boxes framing suspicious lesions were output. Valid areas were further extracted and unnecessary fields were filter out to avoid possible false positives. To predict by case, a logic linking the prediction results of consecutive images was added. Computed tomography (CT) images with the above prediction results were divided into four quadrants, and results would be output only when three consecutive images were predicted to have lesions in the same quadrant. ']"
2020.02.25.20021568-p23-108%4.png	"['Figure 3. Processing and prediction schematic of the model. Raw images were firstly input into the model, and after processing of the model, prediction boxes framing suspicious lesions were output. Valid areas were further extracted and unnecessary fields were filter out to avoid possible false positives. To predict by case, a logic linking the prediction results of consecutive images was added. Computed tomography (CT) images with the above prediction results were divided into four quadrants, and results would be output only when three consecutive images were predicted to have lesions in the same quadrant. ']"
2020.02.25.20021568-p23-108%5.png	"['Figure 3. Processing and prediction schematic of the model. Raw images were firstly input into the model, and after processing of the model, prediction boxes framing suspicious lesions were output. Valid areas were further extracted and unnecessary fields were filter out to avoid possible false positives. To predict by case, a logic linking the prediction results of consecutive images was added. Computed tomography (CT) images with the above prediction results were divided into four quadrants, and results would be output only when three consecutive images were predicted to have lesions in the same quadrant. ']"
2020.02.25.20021568-p23-108%6.png	"['Figure 3. Processing and prediction schematic of the model. Raw images were firstly input into the model, and after processing of the model, prediction boxes framing suspicious lesions were output. Valid areas were further extracted and unnecessary fields were filter out to avoid possible false positives. To predict by case, a logic linking the prediction results of consecutive images was added. Computed tomography (CT) images with the above prediction results were divided into four quadrants, and results would be output only when three consecutive images were predicted to have lesions in the same quadrant. ']"
2020.02.25.20021568-p23-108%7.png	"['Figure 3. Processing and prediction schematic of the model. Raw images were firstly input into the model, and after processing of the model, prediction boxes framing suspicious lesions were output. Valid areas were further extracted and unnecessary fields were filter out to avoid possible false positives. To predict by case, a logic linking the prediction results of consecutive images was added. Computed tomography (CT) images with the above prediction results were divided into four quadrants, and results would be output only when three consecutive images were predicted to have lesions in the same quadrant. ']"
2020.02.25.20021568-p23-108%8.png	"['Figure 3. Processing and prediction schematic of the model. Raw images were firstly input into the model, and after processing of the model, prediction boxes framing suspicious lesions were output. Valid areas were further extracted and unnecessary fields were filter out to avoid possible false positives. To predict by case, a logic linking the prediction results of consecutive images was added. Computed tomography (CT) images with the above prediction results were divided into four quadrants, and results would be output only when three consecutive images were predicted to have lesions in the same quadrant. ']"
2020.02.25.20021568-p23-108%9.png	"['Figure 3. Processing and prediction schematic of the model. Raw images were firstly input into the model, and after processing of the model, prediction boxes framing suspicious lesions were output. Valid areas were further extracted and unnecessary fields were filter out to avoid possible false positives. To predict by case, a logic linking the prediction results of consecutive images was added. Computed tomography (CT) images with the above prediction results were divided into four quadrants, and results would be output only when three consecutive images were predicted to have lesions in the same quadrant. ']"
2020.02.25.20021568-p24-111%0.png	"['Figure 4. Representative images of the model's predictions. A. Computed tomography (CT) images of COVID19 pneumonia. The predictions between the artificial intelligence model and radiologists were consistent. Green boxes, labels from radiologists; red boxes, labels from the model.']"
2020.02.25.20021568-p24-111%1.png	"['Figure 4. Representative images of the model's predictions. A. Computed tomography (CT) images of COVID19 pneumonia. The predictions between the artificial intelligence model and radiologists were consistent. Green boxes, labels from radiologists; red boxes, labels from the model.']"
2020.02.25.20021568-p24-111%2.png	"['Figure 4. Representative images of the model's predictions. A. Computed tomography (CT) images of COVID19 pneumonia. The predictions between the artificial intelligence model and radiologists were consistent. Green boxes, labels from radiologists; red boxes, labels from the model.']"
2020.02.25.20021568-p24-111%3.png	"['Figure 4. Representative images of the model's predictions. A. Computed tomography (CT) images of COVID19 pneumonia. The predictions between the artificial intelligence model and radiologists were consistent. Green boxes, labels from radiologists; red boxes, labels from the model.']"
2020.02.25.20021568-p24-111%4.png	"['Figure 4. Representative images of the model's predictions. A. Computed tomography (CT) images of COVID19 pneumonia. The predictions between the artificial intelligence model and radiologists were consistent. Green boxes, labels from radiologists; red boxes, labels from the model.']"
2020.02.25.20021568-p24-111%5.png	"['Figure 4. Representative images of the model's predictions. B. CT images of the control. The first image is an ordinary bacterial pneumonia, showing a consolidation of the right lower lobe. The second image has a tumorous lesion in the lung, showing a mass in the left upper lobe, with burrs seen at the edges, and showing leaf-like growth with vacuoles inside. The third image is a secondary pulmonary tuberculosis, showing a left apical fibrous cord. The fourth image is a bronchiectasis complicated with infection, showing bronchodilation and expansion, cystic changes, and surrounding patches of infection. The fifth image shows normal lungs. ']"
2020.02.25.20021568-p24-111%6.png	"['Figure 4. Representative images of the model's predictions. B. CT images of the control. The first image is an ordinary bacterial pneumonia, showing a consolidation of the right lower lobe. The second image has a tumorous lesion in the lung, showing a mass in the left upper lobe, with burrs seen at the edges, and showing leaf-like growth with vacuoles inside. The third image is a secondary pulmonary tuberculosis, showing a left apical fibrous cord. The fourth image is a bronchiectasis complicated with infection, showing bronchodilation and expansion, cystic changes, and surrounding patches of infection. The fifth image shows normal lungs. ']"
2020.02.25.20021568-p24-111%7.png	"['Figure 4. Representative images of the model's predictions. B. CT images of the control. The first image is an ordinary bacterial pneumonia, showing a consolidation of the right lower lobe. The second image has a tumorous lesion in the lung, showing a mass in the left upper lobe, with burrs seen at the edges, and showing leaf-like growth with vacuoles inside. The third image is a secondary pulmonary tuberculosis, showing a left apical fibrous cord. The fourth image is a bronchiectasis complicated with infection, showing bronchodilation and expansion, cystic changes, and surrounding patches of infection. The fifth image shows normal lungs. ']"
2020.02.25.20021568-p24-111%8.png	"['Figure 4. Representative images of the model's predictions. B. CT images of the control. The first image is an ordinary bacterial pneumonia, showing a consolidation of the right lower lobe. The second image has a tumorous lesion in the lung, showing a mass in the left upper lobe, with burrs seen at the edges, and showing leaf-like growth with vacuoles inside. The third image is a secondary pulmonary tuberculosis, showing a left apical fibrous cord. The fourth image is a bronchiectasis complicated with infection, showing bronchodilation and expansion, cystic changes, and surrounding patches of infection. The fifth image shows normal lungs. ']"
2020.02.25.20021568-p24-111%9.png	"['Figure 4. Representative images of the model's predictions. B. CT images of the control. The first image is an ordinary bacterial pneumonia, showing a consolidation of the right lower lobe. The second image has a tumorous lesion in the lung, showing a mass in the left upper lobe, with burrs seen at the edges, and showing leaf-like growth with vacuoles inside. The third image is a secondary pulmonary tuberculosis, showing a left apical fibrous cord. The fourth image is a bronchiectasis complicated with infection, showing bronchodilation and expansion, cystic changes, and surrounding patches of infection. The fifth image shows normal lungs. ']"
2020.02.25.20027763-p15-53%0.png	['Figure 2. CT findings in 4 patients with confirmed COVID-19. A. Patchy GGO distributed in subpleural area in left lower lung.']
2020.02.25.20027763-p15-53%1.png	"['Figure 2. CT findings in 4 patients with confirmed COVID-19. B. A round-like, mixed GGO and consolidation lesion (with reversed halo sign) in subpleural area in right lower lung.']"
2020.02.26.20026989-p34-114_1%0.png	"['Figure 3. The relationship of pulmonary inflammation and CRSL characteristics after COVID-19 infected.  A. Computed tomography of the chest of patients with COVID-19. According to the patchy or ground glass shadows in the chest CT images, the patients were divided into < 5 0 % and ≥ 5 0 % groups.']"
2020.02.26.20026989-p34-114_1%1.png	"['Figure 3. The relationship of pulmonary inflammation and CRSL characteristics after COVID-19 infected.  A. Computed tomography of the chest of patients with COVID-19. According to the patchy or ground glass shadows in the chest CT images, the patients were divided into < 5 0 % and ≥ 5 0 % groups.']"
2020.02.26.20026989-p34-114_2%0.png	"['Figure 3. The relationship of pulmonary inflammation and CRSL characteristics after COVID-19 infected.  A. Computed tomography of the chest of patients with COVID-19. According to the patchy or ground glass shadows in the chest CT images, the patients were divided into < 5 0 % and ≥ 5 0 % groups.']"
2020.02.26.20026989-p34-114_2%1.png	"['Figure 3. The relationship of pulmonary inflammation and CRSL characteristics after COVID-19 infected.  A. Computed tomography of the chest of patients with COVID-19. According to the patchy or ground glass shadows in the chest CT images, the patients were divided into < 5 0 % and ≥ 5 0 % groups.']"
2020.02.26.20027938-p6-80_1%0.png	"['Fig. 3 Clinical photographs of the positive patient regarding conjunctivitis and chest CT: (D-F)dynamic changes of peripheral ground-glass opacities in both lungs (yellow arrows) which illuminate the pneumonia caused by SARS-COV-2 infection.The pulmonary lesions were aggravated on the 10th day, and the lesions were basically absorbed on the 18th day. ']"
2020.02.26.20027938-p6-80_1%1.png	"['Fig. 3 Clinical photographs of the positive patient regarding conjunctivitis and chest CT: (D-F)dynamic changes of peripheral ground-glass opacities in both lungs (yellow arrows) which illuminate the pneumonia caused by SARS-COV-2 infection.The pulmonary lesions were aggravated on the 10th day, and the lesions were basically absorbed on the 18th day. ']"
2020.02.26.20027938-p6-80_2%0.png	"['Fig. 3 Clinical photographs of the positive patient regarding conjunctivitis and chest CT: (D-F)dynamic changes of peripheral ground-glass opacities in both lungs (yellow arrows) which illuminate the pneumonia caused by SARS-COV-2 infection.The pulmonary lesions were aggravated on the 10th day, and the lesions were basically absorbed on the 18th day. ']"
2020.02.26.20027938-p6-80_2%1.png	"['Fig. 3 Clinical photographs of the positive patient regarding conjunctivitis and chest CT: (D-F)dynamic changes of peripheral ground-glass opacities in both lungs (yellow arrows) which illuminate the pneumonia caused by SARS-COV-2 infection.The pulmonary lesions were aggravated on the 10th day, and the lesions were basically absorbed on the 18th day. ']"
2020.02.26.20027938-p6-80_3%0.png	"['Fig. 3 Clinical photographs of the positive patient regarding conjunctivitis and chest CT: (D-F)dynamic changes of peripheral ground-glass opacities in both lungs (yellow arrows) which illuminate the pneumonia caused by SARS-COV-2 infection.The pulmonary lesions were aggravated on the 10th day, and the lesions were basically absorbed on the 18th day. ']"
2020.02.26.20027938-p6-80_3%1.png	"['Fig. 3 Clinical photographs of the positive patient regarding conjunctivitis and chest CT: (D-F)dynamic changes of peripheral ground-glass opacities in both lungs (yellow arrows) which illuminate the pneumonia caused by SARS-COV-2 infection.The pulmonary lesions were aggravated on the 10th day, and the lesions were basically absorbed on the 18th day. ']"
2020.02.27.20027557-p25-137%0.png	['Figure 4. Chest CT images in the axial (left panel) and coronal view (right panel) of represented severe COVID-19 patient before and after receiving DIP adjunctive therapy. (A) Initial chest CT scan 10 days before DIP treatment.']
2020.02.27.20027557-p25-137%1.png	['Figure 4. Chest CT images in the axial (left panel) and coronal view (right panel) of represented severe COVID-19 patient before and after receiving DIP adjunctive therapy. (B) Chest CT scan 5 days before DIP treatment.']
2020.02.27.20027557-p25-137%2.png	['Figure 4. Chest CT images in the axial (left panel) and coronal view (right panel) of represented severe COVID-19 patient before and after receiving DIP adjunctive therapy. (C) Chest CT scan 2 days before DIP treatment.']
2020.02.27.20027557-p25-137%3.png	['Figure 4. Chest CT images in the axial (left panel) and coronal view (right panel) of represented severe COVID-19 patient before and after receiving DIP adjunctive therapy. (D) Chest CT scan 2 days after DIP treatment.']
2020.02.27.20027557-p25-137%4.png	['Figure 4. Chest CT images in the axial (left panel) and coronal view (right panel) of represented severe COVID-19 patient before and after receiving DIP adjunctive therapy. (E) Chest CT scan 7 days after DIP treatment.']
2020.02.28.20029025-p23-182.png	"['Figure 7. Patient case CT scan. A: Patient ID 55, the nucleic acid detection result was negative, but the IgM and IgG results were positive. In the lower of both lungs, there were large fuzzy shadows and GGO, some slightly fan-shaped distribution. ']"
2020.02.28.20029025-p23-183.png	"['Figure 7. Patient case CT scan. B: Patient ID 19, the nucleic acid detection result was positive, but the IgM and IgG results were negative, no obvious lesion was found in both lungs. ']"
2020.03.01.20029769-p21-73_1%0.png	"['Figure 4 Variation in IL-6 and chest computed tomography in severe COVID-19 patients. (A) The elevated baseline IL-6 was correlated with the severity assessed by chest computed tomography (CT) scan, and the decrease in IL-6 after treatment was positively correlated with the improvement in chest CT images. ']"
2020.03.01.20029769-p21-73_1%1.png	"['Figure 4 Variation in IL-6 and chest computed tomography in severe COVID-19 patients. (A) The elevated baseline IL-6 was correlated with the severity assessed by chest computed tomography (CT) scan, and the decrease in IL-6 after treatment was positively correlated with the improvement in chest CT images. ']"
2020.03.01.20029769-p21-73_1%2.png	"['Figure 4 Variation in IL-6 and chest computed tomography in severe COVID-19 patients. (A) The elevated baseline IL-6 was correlated with the severity assessed by chest computed tomography (CT) scan, and the decrease in IL-6 after treatment was positively correlated with the improvement in chest CT images. ']"
2020.03.01.20029769-p21-73_2%0.png	"['Figure 4 Variation in IL-6 and chest computed tomography in severe COVID-19 patients. (A) The elevated baseline IL-6 was correlated with the severity assessed by chest computed tomography (CT) scan, and the decrease in IL-6 after treatment was positively correlated with the improvement in chest CT images. ']"
2020.03.01.20029769-p21-73_2%1.png	"['Figure 4 Variation in IL-6 and chest computed tomography in severe COVID-19 patients. (A) The elevated baseline IL-6 was correlated with the severity assessed by chest computed tomography (CT) scan, and the decrease in IL-6 after treatment was positively correlated with the improvement in chest CT images. ']"
2020.03.01.20029769-p21-73_2%2.png	"['Figure 4 Variation in IL-6 and chest computed tomography in severe COVID-19 patients. (A) The elevated baseline IL-6 was correlated with the severity assessed by chest computed tomography (CT) scan, and the decrease in IL-6 after treatment was positively correlated with the improvement in chest CT images. ']"
2020.03.01.20029769-p21-73_3.png	"['Figure 4 Variation in IL-6 and chest computed tomography in severe COVID-19 patients. (B) Three patients showed elevated IL-6 after treatment, which is associated with disease exacerbation and progressed CT imaging. ']"
2020.03.01.20029769-p21-73_4.png	"['Figure 4 Variation in IL-6 and chest computed tomography in severe COVID-19 patients. (B) Three patients showed elevated IL-6 after treatment, which is associated with disease exacerbation and progressed CT imaging. ']"
2020.03.03.20030353-p17-106%0.png	['Figure 1. The typical manifestations in CT and chest X-ray for patients with COVID-19. Cross-sectional CT shows (A) patchy consolidation abutting the pleura in left upper lobe.  ']
2020.03.03.20030353-p17-106%1.png	['Figure 1. The typical manifestations in CT and chest X-ray for patients with COVID-19. Cross-sectional CT shows (B) large areas of consolidation with air bronchogram sign in right upper lobe.  ']
2020.03.03.20030353-p17-106%2.png	['Figure 1. The typical manifestations in CT and chest X-ray for patients with COVID-19. Cross-sectional CT shows (C) Ground glass opacity in bilateral upper lobe.  ']
2020.03.03.20030668-p18-64%0.png	['Figure 1 Typical chest radiographs of a patient. Chest radiographs of one patient on day 1 at ICU admission (A) and day 5 (B); CT scan of chest of the same patient on day 10 and day 20 after ICU admission. ']
2020.03.03.20030668-p18-64%1.png	['Figure 1 Typical chest radiographs of a patient. Chest radiographs of one patient on day 1 at ICU admission (A) and day 5 (B); CT scan of chest of the same patient on day 10 and day 20 after ICU admission. ']
2020.03.03.20030775-p10-88%0.png	"['Figure2. 57-year old man with history of recent travel to Wuhan, presenting with fever, cough and shortness of breath. Axial thin-section non-contrast CT scan shows diffuse bilateral confluent and patchy ground-glass, air-bronchogram and consolidation, characterized by peripheral distribution. Multiple lobes were involved.']"
2020.03.03.20030775-p10-88%1.png	"['Figure2. 57-year old man with history of recent travel to Wuhan, presenting with fever, cough and shortness of breath. Axial thin-section non-contrast CT scan shows diffuse bilateral confluent and patchy ground-glass, air-bronchogram and consolidation, characterized by peripheral distribution. Multiple lobes were involved.']"
2020.03.03.20030775-p11-90%0.png	"['Figure 4. 57-year old man as mild NCP patients with history of recent travel to Wuhan. Ground-glass opacities with a peripheral distribution in bilateral lung (green arrow), and with enlarged image in the upper right corner of A image. Vascular enlargement sign was observed in the lesion located in the left upper lobe, and with enlarged image in the upper left corner of B image (yellow arrow). The lesions in the left lower lobe shows cobblestone/reticular pattern, and with enlarged image in the lower right corner of B image (red yellow).']"
2020.03.03.20030775-p11-90%1.png	"['Figure 4. 57-year old man as mild NCP patients with history of recent travel to Wuhan. Ground-glass opacities with a peripheral distribution in bilateral lung (green arrow), and with enlarged image in the upper right corner of A image. Vascular enlargement sign was observed in the lesion located in the left upper lobe, and with enlarged image in the upper left corner of B image (yellow arrow). The lesions in the left lower lobe shows cobblestone/reticular pattern, and with enlarged image in the lower right corner of B image (red yellow).']"
2020.03.03.20030775-p11-91.png	"['Figure 3. 76-year old man with history of recent travel to Wuhan, presenting with fever and productive cough. Axial thin-section non-contrast CT image shows diffusion lesions in bilateral lung, mainly manifested as ground-glass opacification (red arrow and red line around region), and cobble stone/Reticular pattern (blue arrow and blue line around region). Besides, Vascular enlargement sign was observed in the lesions (yellow arrow).']"
2020.03.03.20030775-p12-93%0.png	"['Figure5. 68-year old female as serve NCP patients with history of recent travel to Wuhan, presenting with fever and productive cough. Axial thin-section non-contrast CT image shows diffusion lesions in bilateral lung. A showed many CT features such as ground-glass opacification, cobblestone/reticular pattern (blue arrow and blue line around region), fibrosis and dilated bronchi with thickened wall (the enlarged image in the upper right corner, red arrow). B showed consolidation (pink arrow) and mixed pattern (yellow arrow and yellow line around region) in the bilateral lower lobes.']"
2020.03.03.20030775-p12-93%1.png	"['Figure5. 68-year old female as serve NCP patients with history of recent travel to Wuhan, presenting with fever and productive cough. Axial thin-section non-contrast CT image shows diffusion lesions in bilateral lung. A showed many CT features such as ground-glass opacification, cobblestone/reticular pattern (blue arrow and blue line around region), fibrosis and dilated bronchi with thickened wall (the enlarged image in the upper right corner, red arrow). B showed consolidation (pink arrow) and mixed pattern (yellow arrow and yellow line around region) in the bilateral lower lobes.']"
2020.03.04.20026005-p12-1946%0.png	"['Figure 2 Chest Computed Tomographic Images of two Discharged Patients of Serious Conditions Infected With NCP. Baseline CT images at admission of the first discharged patient (IP: C56, 57 years) show multiple patchy pure ground glass opacity (GGO), GGO with reticular and/or interlobular septal thickening (A). ']"
2020.03.04.20026005-p12-1946%1.png	"['Figure 2 Chest Computed Tomographic Images of two Discharged Patients of Serious Conditions Infected With NCP. After the disease progressed, Follow-up CT images at 7 day show pulmonary consolidation occurred, lung parenchyma from peripheral to the central lung interstitium (B). ']"
2020.03.04.20026005-p12-1946%2.png	['Figure 2 Chest Computed Tomographic Images of two Discharged Patients of Serious Conditions Infected With NCP. Follow-up CT images at 21 day show most of the lesions were absorbed and some of them showed changes of pulmonary interstitial fibrosis (C). ']
2020.03.04.20026005-p12-1946%3.png	"['Figure 2 Chest Computed Tomographic Images of two Discharged Patients of Serious Conditions Infected With NCP. Baseline CT images at admission of the second discharged patient (IP: C54, 37years) show multiple patchy pure ground glass opacity (GGO), GGO with reticular and/or interlobular septal thickening (D). ']"
2020.03.04.20026005-p12-1946%4.png	"['Figure 2 Chest Computed Tomographic Images of two Discharged Patients of Serious Conditions Infected With NCP. After the disease progressed, Follow-up CT images at 9 day show pulmonary consolidation occurred, from peripheral pulmonary parenchyma to the central lung interstitium (E). ']"
2020.03.04.20026005-p12-1946%5.png	['Figure 2 Chest Computed Tomographic Images of two Discharged Patients of Serious Conditions Infected With NCP. Follow-up CT images at 21 day show most of the lesions were absorbed and some of them showed changes of pulmonary interstitial fibrosis (F). ']
2020.03.04.20030395-p27-108%0%0.png	['Figure 1. Representative chest CT images from multiple patients. Various radiographic abnormalities are present as follows: 1. Intralobular septal thickening and parenchymal bands in the right lower lobe.']
2020.03.04.20030395-p27-108%0%1.png	['Figure 1. Representative chest CT images from multiple patients. Various radiographic abnormalities are present as follows: 2. A small region of subpleural ground glass opacity with partial consolidation in the right lower lobe. ']
2020.03.04.20030395-p27-108%0%2.png	['Figure 1. Representative chest CT images from multiple patients. Various radiographic abnormalities are present as follows: 3. A small region of subpleural consolidation in the posterior right upper lobe.  ']
2020.03.04.20030395-p27-108%0%3.png	"['Figure 1. Representative chest CT images from multiple patients. Various radiographic abnormalities are present as follows: 4. Bilateral multilobular ground glass opacity and partial consolidation, and a pneumatocele in the right upper lobe. ']"
2020.03.04.20030395-p27-108%0%4.png	"['Figure 1. Representative chest CT images from multiple patients. Various radiographic abnormalities are present as follows: 5. Bilateral consolidation in the peripheral regions of the upper lobes, with inter- and intra-lobular septal thickening (crazy paving pattern).']"
2020.03.04.20030395-p27-108%0%5.png	"['Figure 1. Representative chest CT images from multiple patients. Various radiographic abnormalities are present as follows: 6. Bilateral consolidation in the subpleural region of lower lobes, with parenchymal bands. Air bronchograms are present in the right lower lobe.']"
2020.03.04.20030395-p27-108%0%6.png	['Figure 1. Representative chest CT images from multiple patients. Various radiographic abnormalities are present as follows: 7. Diffuse consolidation in the right lower lobe. Ground glass opacity with partial consolidation in multiple lobes of left lung.']
2020.03.04.20030395-p27-108%0%7.png	['Figure 1. Representative chest CT images from multiple patients. Various radiographic abnormalities are present as follows: 8. Bilateral diffuse consolidation with air bronchograms in the lower lobes. Multiple areas of patchy consolidation in the right middle lobe. ']
2020.03.04.20030395-p27-108%0%8.png	['Figure 1. Representative chest CT images from multiple patients. Various radiographic abnormalities are present as follows: 9. Bilateral diffuse consolidation with air bronchograms.']
2020.03.04.20030395-p27-108%0.png	['Figure 1. Representative chest CT images from multiple patients. Various radiographic abnormalities are present as follows: 1. Intralobular septal thickening and parenchymal bands in the right lower lobe.']
2020.03.04.20030395-p27-108%1.png	['Figure 1. Representative chest CT images from multiple patients. Various radiographic abnormalities are present as follows: 2. A small region of subpleural ground glass opacity with partial consolidation in the right lower lobe. ']
2020.03.04.20030395-p27-108%2.png	['Figure 1. Representative chest CT images from multiple patients. Various radiographic abnormalities are present as follows: 3. A small region of subpleural consolidation in the posterior right upper lobe.  ']
2020.03.04.20030395-p27-108%3.png	"['Figure 1. Representative chest CT images from multiple patients. Various radiographic abnormalities are present as follows: 4. Bilateral multilobular ground glass opacity and partial consolidation, and a pneumatocele in the right upper lobe. ']"
2020.03.04.20030395-p27-108%4.png	"['Figure 1. Representative chest CT images from multiple patients. Various radiographic abnormalities are present as follows: 5. Bilateral consolidation in the peripheral regions of the upper lobes, with inter- and intra-lobular septal thickening (crazy paving pattern).']"
2020.03.04.20030395-p27-108%5.png	"['Figure 1. Representative chest CT images from multiple patients. Various radiographic abnormalities are present as follows: 6. Bilateral consolidation in the subpleural region of lower lobes, with parenchymal bands. Air bronchograms are present in the right lower lobe.']"
2020.03.04.20030395-p27-108%6.png	['Figure 1. Representative chest CT images from multiple patients. Various radiographic abnormalities are present as follows: 7. Diffuse consolidation in the right lower lobe. Ground glass opacity with partial consolidation in multiple lobes of left lung.']
2020.03.04.20030395-p27-108%7.png	['Figure 1. Representative chest CT images from multiple patients. Various radiographic abnormalities are present as follows: 8. Bilateral diffuse consolidation with air bronchograms in the lower lobes. Multiple areas of patchy consolidation in the right middle lobe. ']
2020.03.04.20030395-p27-108%8.png	['Figure 1. Representative chest CT images from multiple patients. Various radiographic abnormalities are present as follows: 9. Bilateral diffuse consolidation with air bronchograms.']
2020.03.04.20031039-p23-97_1%0.png	"['Figure 2 A: Chest computed tomographic images obtained from a 47-year-old male patient on day 6 after symptom onset, showed extensive and fused ground glass opacity (red arrow) in both lungs.']"
2020.03.04.20031039-p23-97_1%1.png	"['Figure 2 A: Chest computed tomographic images obtained from a 47-year-old male patient on day 6 after symptom onset, showed extensive and fused ground glass opacity (red arrow) in both lungs.']"
2020.03.04.20031039-p23-97_1%2.png	"['Figure 2 A: Chest computed tomographic images obtained from a 47-year-old male patient on day 6 after symptom onset, showed extensive and fused ground glass opacity (red arrow) in both lungs.']"
2020.03.04.20031039-p23-97_2%0.png	"['Figure 2 B: Chest computed tomographic images obtained from a 59year-old female on day 7 after symptom onset, showed extensive and fused ground glass opacity (red arrow) in both lungs.']"
2020.03.04.20031039-p23-97_2%1.png	"['Figure 2 B: Chest computed tomographic images obtained from a 59year-old female on day 7 after symptom onset, showed extensive and fused ground glass opacity (red arrow) in both lungs.']"
2020.03.04.20031039-p23-97_2%2.png	"['Figure 2 B: Chest computed tomographic images obtained from a 59year-old female on day 7 after symptom onset, showed extensive and fused ground glass opacity (red arrow) in both lungs.']"
2020.03.04.20031047-p12-81%0.png	"['FIGURE 1, Typical imaging for heart failure and COVID-19 pneumonia. A, Heart failure with bilateral diffuse disease. The disease presented with a gradient distribution and partial GGO and consolidation inside, accompanied with subpleural effusion. Peribronchovascular and septal thickening were also found. ']"
2020.03.04.20031047-p12-81%1.png	"['FIGURE 1, Typical imaging for heart failure and COVID-19 pneumonia. B, Heart failure with bilateral diffuse GGO disease. Peribronchovascular thickening, clear interlobular septal thickening even fissural thickening were found without subpleural effusion. ']"
2020.03.04.20031047-p12-81%2.png	"['FIGURE 1, Typical imaging for heart failure and COVID-19 pneumonia. C, COVID-19 with single rounded subpleural GGO in left lung.']"
2020.03.04.20031047-p12-81%3.png	"['FIGURE 1, Typical imaging for heart failure and COVID-19 pneumonia. D, COVID-19 with rounded GGO in bilateral lungs, partial consolidation was found inside.']"
2020.03.04.20031047-p13-84%0.png	"['FIGURE 2, Different imaging features for heart failure and COVID-19. A, Big patchy GGO in left lung and sporadic GGO in right lung. Peribronchovascular thickening, fissural thickening (arrow) were also found with subpleural effusion.']"
2020.03.04.20031047-p13-84%1.png	"['FIGURE 2, Different imaging features for heart failure and COVID-19. B, Subpleural GGO with band-shaped morphology (arrow) in the dorsal segment of bilateral lungs. Interlobular septal thickening and cardiac enlargement were also found.']"
2020.03.04.20031047-p13-84%2.png	"['FIGURE 2, Different imaging features for heart failure and COVID-19. C, Patchy lesion of Crazy Paving Pattern in right upper lung with partial consolidation inside. Small pulmonary vein enlargement (arrow) was also found, accompanied with subpleural effusion in the right lung. ']"
2020.03.04.20031047-p13-84%3.png	"['FIGURE 2, Different imaging features for heart failure and COVID-19. D, Big patchy GGO in left lung. Interlobular septal thickening was also found inside.']"
2020.03.04.20031047-p13-84%4.png	"['FIGURE 2, Different imaging features for heart failure and COVID-19. E, Multiple disease mixed with GGO and consolidation in bilateral lungs.  Fibrous lesion (arrow) was found in the left lung.']"
2020.03.04.20031047-p13-84%5.png	"['FIGURE 2, Different imaging features for heart failure and COVID-19. F, Patchy lesion of Crazy Paving Pattern in left upper lung with partial consolidation inside.']"
2020.03.04.20031047-p14-87%0.png	"['FIGURE 3, CT imaging of a patient with both heart failure and COVID-19. A, Diffuse disease mixed with GGO and consolidation in bilateral upper lungs, accompanied with interlobular septal thickening and subpleural effusion.']"
2020.03.04.20031047-p14-87%1.png	"['FIGURE 3, CT imaging of a patient with both heart failure and COVID-19. B, Big patchy GGO with irregular morphology in bilateral lungs. Peribronchovascular thickening and subpleural effusion were also found. ']"
2020.03.07.20031393-p7-50%0.png	"['Figure 4: Chest CTs of a asymptomatic patient, obtained on Fab 10 showed small patchy high density shadows and ground glass shadows in the lower lobe of the right lung near the pleural surface.']"
2020.03.07.20031393-p7-50%1.png	"['Figure 4: Chest CTs of a asymptomatic patient, obtained on Fab 10 showed small patchy high density shadows and ground glass shadows in the lower lobe of the right lung near the pleural surface.']"
2020.03.07.20031393-p7-50%2.png	"['Figure 4: Chest CTs of a asymptomatic patient, obtained on Fab 10 showed small patchy high density shadows and ground glass shadows in the lower lobe of the right lung near the pleural surface.']"
2020.03.07.20031393-p7-50%3.png	"['Figure 4: Chest CTs of a asymptomatic patient, obtained on Fab 10 showed small patchy high density shadows and ground glass shadows in the lower lobe of the right lung near the pleural surface.']"
2020.03.08.20031658-p15-103.png	['Figure 1. Representative chest radiographic manifestations in mild and severe cases with COVID-19. ']
2020.03.08.20031658-p15-104.png	['Figure 1. Representative chest radiographic manifestations in mild and severe cases with COVID-19. ']
2020.03.08.20031658-p15-105.png	['Figure 1. Representative chest radiographic manifestations in mild and severe cases with COVID-19. ']
2020.03.08.20031658-p15-106.png	['Figure 1. Representative chest radiographic manifestations in mild and severe cases with COVID-19. ']
2020.03.09.20033118-p20-93%0.png	"['Figure 1: Transverse thin-section CT scans in medical staffs infected with COVID-19 pneumonia. (A) 27-year-old woman: bilateral, peripheral ground-glass opacity in the right lower lobe and left upper lobe (arrow).']"
2020.03.09.20033118-p20-93%1.png	['Figure 1: Transverse thin-section CT scans in medical staffs infected with COVID-19 pneumonia. (B) 41-year-old woman: focal ground-glass opacity associated with smooth interlobular and intralobular septal thickening (crazy-paving pattern).']
2020.03.09.20033118-p20-93%2.png	"['Figure 1: Transverse thin-section CT scans in medical staffs infected with COVID-19 pneumonia. (C) 55-year-old man: bilateral, peripheral ground-glass opacity mixed consolidation pattern.']"
2020.03.09.20033118-p20-93%3.png	"['Figure 1: Transverse thin-section CT scans in medical staffs infected with COVID-19 pneumonia. (D) 28-year-old man: bilateral and linear consolidations in the right and left upper lobes (arrow), regarded as chronic lung lesion with lack of changes on serial CT examinations.']"
2020.03.10.20032136-p34-118%0.png	"['Figure 1. Chest computed tomographic (CT) images for study patients infected with COVID-19. Panel A depicted the chest CT images for a patient aged 21 years on day 10 after illness onset, and Panel B depicted the chest CT images for a patient aged 33 years on day 14 after illness onset.']"
2020.03.10.20032136-p34-118%1.png	"['Figure 1. Chest computed tomographic (CT) images for study patients infected with COVID-19. Panel A depicted the chest CT images for a patient aged 21 years on day 10 after illness onset, and Panel B depicted the chest CT images for a patient aged 33 years on day 14 after illness onset.']"
2020.03.10.20032136-p34-118%2.png	"['Figure 1. Chest computed tomographic (CT) images for study patients infected with COVID-19. Panel A depicted the chest CT images for a patient aged 21 years on day 10 after illness onset, and Panel B depicted the chest CT images for a patient aged 33 years on day 14 after illness onset.']"
2020.03.10.20032136-p34-118%3.png	"['Figure 1. Chest computed tomographic (CT) images for study patients infected with COVID-19. Panel A depicted the chest CT images for a patient aged 21 years on day 10 after illness onset, and Panel B depicted the chest CT images for a patient aged 33 years on day 14 after illness onset.']"
2020.03.10.20032136-p34-118_1%0.png	"['Figure 1. Chest computed tomographic (CT) images for study patients infected with COVID-19. Panel A depicted the chest CT images for a patient aged 21 years on day 10 after illness onset, and Panel B depicted the chest CT images for a patient aged 33 years on day 14 after illness onset.']"
2020.03.10.20032136-p34-118_1%1.png	"['Figure 1. Chest computed tomographic (CT) images for study patients infected with COVID-19. Panel A depicted the chest CT images for a patient aged 21 years on day 10 after illness onset, and Panel B depicted the chest CT images for a patient aged 33 years on day 14 after illness onset.']"
2020.03.10.20032136-p34-118_2%0.png	"['Figure 1. Chest computed tomographic (CT) images for study patients infected with COVID-19. Panel A depicted the chest CT images for a patient aged 21 years on day 10 after illness onset, and Panel B depicted the chest CT images for a patient aged 33 years on day 14 after illness onset.']"
2020.03.10.20032136-p34-118_2%1.png	"['Figure 1. Chest computed tomographic (CT) images for study patients infected with COVID-19. Panel A depicted the chest CT images for a patient aged 21 years on day 10 after illness onset, and Panel B depicted the chest CT images for a patient aged 33 years on day 14 after illness onset.']"
2020.03.11.20033159-p12-45%0.png	"['Figure 1. Transverse Chest Computed Tomographic Images. CT image from case 1 on day 1 after symptom onset, showing delicate patches of ground glass opacity of lower lobe of right lung near the pleura (1A, red arrow).']"
2020.03.11.20033159-p12-45%1.png	"['Figure 1. Transverse Chest Computed Tomographic Images. After receiving treatment for 10 days, the lesions were completely absorbed(1B).']"
2020.03.11.20033159-p12-45%2.png	"['Figure 1. Transverse Chest Computed Tomographic Images. Case 2 showed ground glass consolidation of the left lower lobe near the pleura on Admission (2A, red arrow).']"
2020.03.11.20033159-p12-45%3.png	['Figure 1. Transverse Chest Computed Tomographic Images. Complete resolution of lesion was observed after treatment for 13 days (2B).']
2020.03.11.20033159-p12-45%4.png	['Figure 1. Transverse Chest Computed Tomographic Images. There was no obvious abnormality in bilateral lung fields of case 3 on admission (3A).']
2020.03.11.20033159-p12-45%5.png	['Figure 1. Transverse Chest Computed Tomographic Images. No change in CT imaging was observed during patient's hospitalization (3B).']
2020.03.12.20027185-p8-216.png	['Figure 5: Some accurate and erroneous predictions of the proposed DeCoVNet.']
2020.03.12.20027185-p8-217.png	['Figure 5: Some accurate and erroneous predictions of the proposed DeCoVNet.']
2020.03.12.20027185-p8-218.png	['Figure 5: Some accurate and erroneous predictions of the proposed DeCoVNet.']
2020.03.12.20027185-p8-221.png	['Figure 5: Some accurate and erroneous predictions of the proposed DeCoVNet.']
2020.03.12.20034686-p17-91-3.png	['Fig 2. Typical Features of CT Images of Paediatric Patients with COVID-19.']
2020.03.12.20034686-p17-91-4.png	['Fig 2. Typical Features of CT Images of Paediatric Patients with COVID-19.']
2020.03.12.20034686-p17-91-5.png	['Fig 2. Typical Features of CT Images of Paediatric Patients with COVID-19.']
2020.03.12.20034686-p17-91-6.png	['Fig 2. Typical Features of CT Images of Paediatric Patients with COVID-19.']
2020.03.13.20035212-p23-152.png	['Figure 4. The course of chest CT images of case 8. (A) Images from January 26 show bilateral pleural effusion and pericardial effusion.']
2020.03.13.20035212-p23-153.png	['Figure 4. The course of chest CT images of case 8. (A) Images from January 26 show bilateral pleural effusion and pericardial effusion.']
2020.03.13.20035212-p23-154.png	['Figure 4. The course of chest CT images of case 8. (A) Images from January 26 show bilateral pleural effusion and pericardial effusion.']
2020.03.13.20035212-p23-155.png	['Figure 4. The course of chest CT images of case 8. (B) Images from February 3 show bilateral pleural effusion and pericardial effusion with a small area of ground-glass opacity in the left upper lung.']
2020.03.13.20035212-p23-156.png	['Figure 4. The course of chest CT images of case 8. (B) Images from February 3 show bilateral pleural effusion and pericardial effusion with a small area of ground-glass opacity in the left upper lung.']
2020.03.13.20035212-p23-157.png	['Figure 4. The course of chest CT images of case 8. (B) Images from February 3 show bilateral pleural effusion and pericardial effusion with a small area of ground-glass opacity in the left upper lung.']
2020.03.13.20035212-p23-158.png	['Figure 4. The course of chest CT images of case 8. (C) Images from February 7 show increased ground-glass opacity of the left upper lung with bilateral pleural effusion. A small area of new ground-glass opacity appeared in the right lung.']
2020.03.13.20035212-p23-159.png	['Figure 4. The course of chest CT images of case 8. (C) Images from February 7 show increased ground-glass opacity of the left upper lung with bilateral pleural effusion. A small area of new ground-glass opacity appeared in the right lung.']
2020.03.13.20035212-p23-160.png	['Figure 4. The course of chest CT images of case 8. (C) Images from February 7 show increased ground-glass opacity of the left upper lung with bilateral pleural effusion. A small area of new ground-glass opacity appeared in the right lung.']
2020.03.13.20035212-p23-161.png	"['Figure 4. The course of chest CT images of case 8. (D) Images from February 11 show the further enlarged ground-glass opacity of the left upper lung. New ground-glass opacity is visible in the rest areas of lungs. The left pleural effusion decreased, and the right pleural effusion increased.']"
2020.03.13.20035212-p23-162.png	"['Figure 4. The course of chest CT images of case 8. (D) Images from February 11 show the further enlarged ground-glass opacity of the left upper lung. New ground-glass opacity is visible in the rest areas of lungs. The left pleural effusion decreased, and the right pleural effusion increased.']"
2020.03.13.20035212-p23-163.png	"['Figure 4. The course of chest CT images of case 8. (D) Images from February 11 show the further enlarged ground-glass opacity of the left upper lung. New ground-glass opacity is visible in the rest areas of lungs. The left pleural effusion decreased, and the right pleural effusion increased.']"
2020.03.16.20035105-p6-64-1.png	"['Figure 1. Chest CT imaging of the patient with COVID-19. Chest CT showed patchy high-density blurred shadow in the upper lobe of the left lung (Figure 1A) and patchy ground glass shadow in the anterior segment of the upper lobe of the right lung (Figure 1B). After treatment, chest CT showed that the previous lesions were almost absorbed. ']"
2020.03.16.20035105-p6-64-2.png	"['Figure 1. Chest CT imaging of the patient with COVID-19. Chest CT showed patchy high-density blurred shadow in the upper lobe of the left lung (Figure 1A) and patchy ground glass shadow in the anterior segment of the upper lobe of the right lung (Figure 1B). After treatment, chest CT showed that the previous lesions were almost absorbed. ']"
2020.03.16.20035105-p6-64-3.png	"['Figure 1. Chest CT imaging of the patient with COVID-19. Chest CT showed patchy high-density blurred shadow in the upper lobe of the left lung (Figure 1A) and patchy ground glass shadow in the anterior segment of the upper lobe of the right lung (Figure 1B). After treatment, chest CT showed that the previous lesions were almost absorbed. ']"
2020.03.16.20035105-p6-64-4.png	"['Figure 1. Chest CT imaging of the patient with COVID-19. Chest CT showed patchy high-density blurred shadow in the upper lobe of the left lung (Figure 1A) and patchy ground glass shadow in the anterior segment of the upper lobe of the right lung (Figure 1B). After treatment, chest CT showed that the previous lesions were almost absorbed. ']"
2020.03.16.20036145-p19-128-1.png	['Figure 1.Chest CTs of two patients (A) Chest CT of patient 9 obtained on Feb 9 (7 dpoi) before convalescent plasma transfusion (10 dpoi)showed ground glass opacity with uneven density involving the multilobal segments of both lungs. The heart shadow outline was not clear. The lesion was close to the pleura.']
2020.03.16.20036145-p19-128-2.png	['Figure 1.Chest CTs of two patients (B) CT Image of patient 9 taken on Feb 15(13 dpoi) showed the absorption of bilateral ground glassopacity after convalescent plasma transfusion. ']
2020.03.16.20036145-p19-128-3.png	['Figure 1.Chest CTs of two patients (C)Chest CT of patient 10 was obtained on Feb 8 (19 dpoi) before convalescent plasma transfusion (20 dpoi). The brightness of both lungs was diffusely decreased and multiple shadows of high density in both lungs were observed. ']
2020.03.16.20036145-p19-128-4.png	['Figure 1.Chest CTs of two patients (D) Chest CTof patient 10 on Feb 18 (29dpoi) showed those lesions improvedafter convalescent plasma transfusion. ']
2020.03.18.20038125-p15-54-1.png	"['Figure 1. The CT pattern of abnormal lung findings among asymptomatic patients with COVID-19. A patient 73 years old, female. The patchy non-segmental ground grass opacity (GGO) adjacent to the parietal pleura in the right upper lobe (A and B), and in both lower lobes (C and D). ']"
2020.03.18.20038125-p15-54-2.png	"['Figure 1. The CT pattern of abnormal lung findings among asymptomatic patients with COVID-19. A patient 73 years old, female. The patchy non-segmental ground grass opacity (GGO) adjacent to the parietal pleura in the right upper lobe (A and B), and in both lower lobes (C and D). ']"
2020.03.18.20038125-p15-54-3.png	"['Figure 1. The CT pattern of abnormal lung findings among asymptomatic patients with COVID-19. A patient 73 years old, female. The patchy non-segmental ground grass opacity (GGO) adjacent to the parietal pleura in the right upper lobe (A and B), and in both lower lobes (C and D). ']"
2020.03.18.20038125-p15-54-4.png	"['Figure 1. The CT pattern of abnormal lung findings among asymptomatic patients with COVID-19. A patient 73 years old, female. The patchy non-segmental ground grass opacity (GGO) adjacent to the parietal pleura in the right upper lobe (A and B), and in both lower lobes (C and D). ']"
2020.03.18.20038125-p15-54-5.png	"['Figure 1. The CT pattern of abnormal lung findings among asymptomatic patients with COVID-19. A patient 70 years old, female. The GGO with interlobular septal thickening (crazy-paving appearance) adjacent to the parietal pleura in the both lower lobes (E).']"
2020.03.18.20038125-p15-54-6.png	"['Figure 1. The CT pattern of abnormal lung findings among asymptomatic patients with COVID-19. A patient 76 years old, male. CT scan showed the GGO with consolidation, bronchial wall thickening, and bronchiectasis in the left lower lobe (F).']"
2020.03.18.20038125-p16-56-1.png	"['Figure 2. The progress of CT findings in a patient with COVID-19. A male patient 75 years old was asymptomatic on the admission day. On the fourth day of admission, he showed tachypnea and hypoxemia, and treated oxygen therapy. On the admission day, Chest CT scan showed multifocal GGO adjacent to the parietal pleura in multiple lobes with emphysematous changes (A, B and C).']"
2020.03.18.20038125-p16-56-2.png	"['Figure 2. The progress of CT findings in a patient with COVID-19. A male patient 75 years old was asymptomatic on the admission day. On the fourth day of admission, he showed tachypnea and hypoxemia, and treated oxygen therapy. On the admission day, Chest CT scan showed multifocal GGO adjacent to the parietal pleura in multiple lobes with emphysematous changes (A, B and C).']"
2020.03.18.20038125-p16-56-3.png	"['Figure 2. The progress of CT findings in a patient with COVID-19. A male patient 75 years old was asymptomatic on the admission day. On the fourth day of admission, he showed tachypnea and hypoxemia, and treated oxygen therapy. On the admission day, Chest CT scan showed multifocal GGO adjacent to the parietal pleura in multiple lobes with emphysematous changes (A, B and C).']"
2020.03.18.20038125-p16-56-4.png	"['Figure 2. The progress of CT findings in a patient with COVID-19. On the tenth day of admission, a follow-up chest CT scan showed an increase of extent of GGO with crazy-paving appearance (D, E and F).']"
2020.03.18.20038125-p16-56-5.png	"['Figure 2. The progress of CT findings in a patient with COVID-19. On the tenth day of admission, a follow-up chest CT scan showed an increase of extent of GGO with crazy-paving appearance (D, E and F).']"
2020.03.18.20038125-p16-56-6.png	"['Figure 2. The progress of CT findings in a patient with COVID-19. On the tenth day of admission, a follow-up chest CT scan showed an increase of extent of GGO with crazy-paving appearance (D, E and F).']"
2020.03.19.20038539-p10-57.png	['Figure 2. Chest Computed Tomographic Images of a 50-Year-Old Severe Patient Infected With Coronavirus Disease 2019. ']
2020.03.19.20038539-p10-58.png	['Figure 2. Chest Computed Tomographic Images of a 50-Year-Old Severe Patient Infected With Coronavirus Disease 2019. ']
2020.03.19.20038539-p10-59.png	['Figure 2. Chest Computed Tomographic Images of a 50-Year-Old Severe Patient Infected With Coronavirus Disease 2019. ']
2020.03.19.20038539-p10-60.png	['Figure 2. Chest Computed Tomographic Images of a 50-Year-Old Severe Patient Infected With Coronavirus Disease 2019. ']
2020.03.19.20038539-p10-61.png	['Figure 2. Chest Computed Tomographic Images of a 50-Year-Old Severe Patient Infected With Coronavirus Disease 2019. ']
2020.03.19.20038539-p10-62.png	['Figure 2. Chest Computed Tomographic Images of a 50-Year-Old Severe Patient Infected With Coronavirus Disease 2019. ']
2020.03.20.20037325-p23-121.png	"['Figure 4: Representative cases without malignant progression (A, B) and with malignant']"
2020.03.20.20037325-p23-122.png	"['Figure 4: Representative cases without malignant progression (A, B) and with malignant']"
2020.03.20.20037325-p23-123.png	"['Figure 4: Representative cases without malignant progression (A, B) and with malignant']"
2020.03.20.20037325-p23-124.png	"['Figure 4: Representative cases without malignant progression (A, B) and with malignant']"
2020.03.21.20040691-p18-6-6.png	"['Figure 4: Chest CT image Transverse chest CT images from a 65-year-old male patient showing bilateral large flaky ground glass shadows and consolidation on baseline period. At day 22, the intrapulmonary lesions were significantly absorbed and dissipated by meplazumab add- on treatment.']"
2020.03.21.20040691-p18-67-1.png	"['Figure 4: Chest CT image Transverse chest CT images from a 65-year-old male patient showing bilateral large flaky ground glass shadows and consolidation on baseline period. At day 22, the intrapulmonary lesions were significantly absorbed and dissipated by meplazumab add- on treatment.']"
2020.03.21.20040691-p18-67-2.png	"['Figure 4: Chest CT image Transverse chest CT images from a 65-year-old male patient showing bilateral large flaky ground glass shadows and consolidation on baseline period. At day 22, the intrapulmonary lesions were significantly absorbed and dissipated by meplazumab add- on treatment.']"
2020.03.21.20040691-p18-67-3.png	"['Figure 4: Chest CT image Transverse chest CT images from a 65-year-old male patient showing bilateral large flaky ground glass shadows and consolidation on baseline period. At day 22, the intrapulmonary lesions were significantly absorbed and dissipated by meplazumab add- on treatment.']"
2020.03.21.20040691-p18-67-4.png	"['Figure 4: Chest CT image Transverse chest CT images from a 65-year-old male patient showing bilateral large flaky ground glass shadows and consolidation on baseline period. At day 22, the intrapulmonary lesions were significantly absorbed and dissipated by meplazumab add- on treatment.']"
2020.03.21.20040691-p18-67-5.png	"['Figure 4: Chest CT image Transverse chest CT images from a 65-year-old male patient showing bilateral large flaky ground glass shadows and consolidation on baseline period. At day 22, the intrapulmonary lesions were significantly absorbed and dissipated by meplazumab add- on treatment.']"
2020.03.21.20040691-p18-67-7.png	"['Figure 4: Chest CT image Transverse chest CT images from a 65-year-old male patient showing bilateral large flaky ground glass shadows and consolidation on baseline period. At day 22, the intrapulmonary lesions were significantly absorbed and dissipated by meplazumab add- on treatment.']"
2020.03.21.20040691-p18-67-8.png	"['Figure 4: Chest CT image Transverse chest CT images from a 65-year-old male patient showing bilateral large flaky ground glass shadows and consolidation on baseline period. At day 22, the intrapulmonary lesions were significantly absorbed and dissipated by meplazumab add- on treatment.']"
2020.03.22.20034041-p16-66.png	['Figure 2 Natural patient receiving danoprevir/ritonavir plus interferon nebulization (Patient 1)  ']
2020.03.22.20034041-p17-80-1.png	['Figure 3 Experienced patient treated with lopinavir/ritonavir plus interferon nebulization for 3 days and switched to danoprevir/ritonavir plus interferon nebulization. ']
2020.03.22.20034041-p17-80-2.png	['Figure 3 Experienced patient treated with lopinavir/ritonavir plus interferon nebulization for 3 days and switched to danoprevir/ritonavir plus interferon nebulization. ']
2020.03.22.20034041-p18-92-1.png	"['Figure 4 Patient failed lopinavir/ritonavir plus interferon nebulization and switched to danoprevir/ritonavir without interferon nebulization (Patient 8) GGO, ground-glass opacity. Red arrows indicate the possible lesions. * Viral RNA was undetectable in both nasal and phlegm swabs. ']"
2020.03.22.20034041-p18-92-2.png	"['Figure 4 Patient failed lopinavir/ritonavir plus interferon nebulization and switched to danoprevir/ritonavir without interferon nebulization (Patient 8) GGO, ground-glass opacity. Red arrows indicate the possible lesions. * Viral RNA was undetectable in both nasal and phlegm swabs. ']"
2020.03.22.20034041-p18-92-3.png	"['Figure 4 Patient failed lopinavir/ritonavir plus interferon nebulization and switched to danoprevir/ritonavir without interferon nebulization (Patient 8) GGO, ground-glass opacity. Red arrows indicate the possible lesions. * Viral RNA was undetectable in both nasal and phlegm swabs. ']"
2020.03.22.20040782-p24-1533-1.png	"['Figure 1 Various chest CT imaging features of COVID-19 GGO, ground glass opacity A, GGO with bilateral and subpleural distribution']"
2020.03.22.20040782-p24-1533-2.png	"['Figure 1 Various chest CT imaging features of COVID-19 GGO, ground glass opacity B, crazy-paving pattern with subpleural and bilateral lower pulmonary distribution']"
2020.03.22.20040782-p24-1533-3.png	"['Figure 1 Various chest CT imaging features of COVID-19 GGO, ground glass opacity C, GGO']"
2020.03.22.20040782-p24-1533-4.png	"['Figure 1 Various chest CT imaging features of COVID-19 GGO, ground glass opacity D, GGO with bilateral and subpleural distribution']"
2020.03.22.20040782-p24-1533-5.png	"['Figure 1 Various chest CT imaging features of COVID-19 GGO, ground glass opacity E, GGO with crazy-paving pattern and air bronchogram']"
2020.03.22.20040782-p24-1533-6.png	"['Figure 1 Various chest CT imaging features of COVID-19 GGO, ground glass opacity F, GGO with consolidation']"
2020.03.22.20040782-p24-1533-7.png	"['Figure 1 Various chest CT imaging features of COVID-19 GGO, ground glass opacity G, GGO with air bronchogram and subpleural distribution']"
2020.03.22.20040782-p24-1533-8.png	"['Figure 1 Various chest CT imaging features of COVID-19 GGO, ground glass opacity H, GGO with unilateral and subpleural distribution']"
2020.03.22.20040782-p25-1541.png	"['Figure 1 Various chest CT imaging features of COVID-19 GGO, ground glass opacity ']"
2020.03.22.20040782-p25-1542.png	"['Figure 1 Various chest CT imaging features of COVID-19 GGO, ground glass opacity ']"
2020.03.22.20040782-p25-1543.png	"['Figure 1 Various chest CT imaging features of COVID-19 GGO, ground glass opacity ']"
2020.03.22.20040782-p25-1544.png	"['Figure 1 Various chest CT imaging features of COVID-19 GGO, ground glass opacity ']"
2020.03.22.20040782-p25-1545.png	"['Figure 1 Various chest CT imaging features of COVID-19 GGO, ground glass opacity ']"
2020.03.22.20040782-p25-1546.png	"['Figure 1 Various chest CT imaging features of COVID-19 GGO, ground glass opacity ']"